Good evening.
How's everybody doing?
I was gonna open this coke but it's unfortunately a coke with a timer so and it's unspecified timer so I opened it but I'm not sure when it will actually be open.
I guess we'll have to wait and see.
How you doing?
Can't believe there's no him emoji.
I was uh I haven't done that yet yeah I'm also working on another emoji that people suggested which is like a brain with a question mark in it.
I tend to forget things sometimes and people like to remind me of that so yeah I'm working on those.
It's gonna be awesome.
I think I have a pretty good one already but I just want to make it even better.
But yeah we definitely need a him emoji.
It's become a bit of a meme now.
Exactly coke can with trigger.
When open it casts another spell.
Yeah exactly.
I understand triggers.
I understand timers.
In fact I am most looking forward to understanding more.
Just the understanding is driving me crazy.
I am obsessed with this game.
I told you this last time but goddamn it's on my mind constantly.
Hey news of PE.
I'm glad I kept recommending it to you.
You're playing it makes me so happy and I have a smile the whole time I'm watching you play.
Please marry me.
Okay well we're gonna get married.
We're gonna get married at all who's pleasant.
That's fine.
What's up Roy?
Youkso.
I'm proud of petitioning the him is emote.
You were the one doing that.
Nice.
I'm proud of you for doing it.
It's a good emote.
We gotta put it in.
Hummus?
Oh that's different.
Damn so soon.
You know like we talked about in tunic.
Segments?
You gotta go straight to the sex.
I mean wedding.
Oh my god.
This is getting weird.
I just I honestly I just want to play.
I have one question for you guys and I'm looking for an answer.
You can answer me.
Is there a way in the game to see my progression to see the spells I've unlocked and all the enemies?
I was sitting here in the menu.
I can't find it.
Am I stupid?
How do I see it?
I've clicked everything.
Oh after run.
So I can't right now.
So I can't do it right now.
Aha.
Okay thanks.
I was losing my mind because I felt there's gotta be a way to just see the stuff that I can usually see.
So okay that's all I needed to know.
Guess I can see it during a run.
That sounds good.
Man we're gonna be doing runs today.
Holy shit.
It's gonna be great.
I'm gonna get so far.
I'm gonna do so much experimentation and I have plans to go all kinds of places.
The exploration in this game is off the charts.
This is some next-level exploration feeling and I love it.
Yeah.
So I'm sorry but I'm just gonna close you guys down and jump into the game.
So here it is.
New game.
Wait what are these other ones?
Daily run.
New day new world.
Some starting items are randomized.
Every player is playing.
That's actually kind of cool.
I guess if you've beaten the game once it would be cool to do this knowing everyone else has the same seed.
That would be awesome actually.
Daily practice run.
Rent you can try this.
Hmm weird.
I'm just gonna new game.
Here we go.
New game.
Yep.
Okay we're back.
Let me actually activate my keyboard.
I always use a computer just with the mouse but I had to buy a keyboard for this game because it uses one.
So let me activate it.
There you go.
I'm not used to using a keyboard at all.
It's like very foreign to me.
So yeah.
This what it is.
Keyboard.
Here we go.
I usually use the on-screen keyboard thing in Windows for things.
Okay so let me see here.
Spark bolt.
And TNT.
I think this one explodes when it hits something so I can make it make my way up here.
Hell yeah.
Go here and then up here.
And watch this.
Fucking love this game.
This sound effect is so satisfying.
Why is it so good?
That's what I want to know.
Dude you can even hear it here.
Listen.
Oh I need to do that.
In fact I can make it come to me.
Plump.
There we go.
You found a familiar orb of true knowledge.
Nice.
Is it?
I wonder if it's always a mag.
Wait where did that thing go?
Didn't the tablet fall down?
Am I crazy?
Maybe it rolled all down the hill.
That's probably what happened.
Is there anything else I want to do here?
I don't think so.
No I'm gonna go back down now.
Okay.
Why does it feel like I'm angering some kind of fucking demon deep on the ground every time I do this?
Oh here it is.
Is it the same?
Wait.
Is this different?
It is true without lying.
Certain and most true.
That which is below is like that which... oh I have read this one.
Volume one.
Okay.
So I could take this up there and put it on the thing and it gives me a hundred gold.
That's what I found out last time.
But I'm... you know what?
I want to try and take other things up there.
There's got to be more secrets.
But I guess it's got to be things you can pick up.
Otherwise it doesn't really work.
Enter the mines.
We are back baby.
Straight with the music.
Oh we've got a guy down there.
I need to know what this guy's name is.
Hold on.
Maybe I can see that now.
Progress.
Let's see if we can find him.
Haiku horta.
So I'm just gonna call him Haiku.
This is Haiku.
What's up Haiku?
Haiku horta.
And then we have Hemis.
Those are the two names I know now.
Hold on.
Let me actually check the other ones real quick.
I just want to see.
Okay.
We have the Howley Cohesi.
Howley Cohesi?
Okay.
So this is Horta.
This is Howley Cohesi.
Because they're all like Haiku it seems.
Horta.
No wait.
This is Horta.
Oh I'm so confused.
This is gonna be learning Finnish.
The stream.
I want right here.
Holy shit.
And it's rain cloud.
Damn dude.
I like it.
We can use that to cross the lava.
And do other... What's that?
What the hell is that?
Hello?
Wait.
Broke.
Oh broken wand.
Wait a minute.
We gotta take care of that guy.
And I'm gonna be playing so patient today.
I'm not gonna die a single time.
Watch.
You see that?
You see the wheel?
Plant.
Gotcha.
Let's see the broken wand.
This wand has snapped in half but it still crackles with magical energy.
So that's gonna throw it and it's gonna do some crazy shit when it lands right?
Let's try it.
Awesome.
It shoots arrows.
That's pretty cool.
We can use that to clear a very secluded confined room.
I should say.
I'm gonna go so slow.
We're gonna do this so good.
There we go.
Take care of that horta.
Where are the himis?
Uh there's something up there as well that I want to grab.
Oh there's a bunch of these hortas.
It's gonna mean something like zombie dog or something.
Because they look like dogs but they're zombies.
Actually hold on.
Did I just hit that nail on the head?
Because watch.
Heiku horta?
Horta.
This guy seems more green.
So maybe that's like a zombie and this is...
I don't know.
Finnish people will know.
I wonder if this game is weird to play as a Finnish person.
Is it like off-putting to read this in Finnish I wonder?
And be like hey I know what that means.
It's not as mysterious I guess.
Just like everyday stuff you know.
I heard this is the Finland simulator.
This is how it is over there.
I know that's kind of a lie because I've been there quite a lot.
So I don't know what those people are smoking.
Okay I'm sort of going back and forth for some reason right now.
I need to explore in one direction and finish that direction.
We've got a dude.
Did I hit something?
Goddamn.
Where'd you go?
Holy shit.
Played slow, played safe.
Wait I took damage right there.
Dude I keep hitting the projectile in the air with my wand.
I was actually muted.
Unfortunately I have no idea how long I was muted for but I saw it on the left.
I apologize.
I was basically talking shit about Finland for a moment.
Or about the people saying that this game looks like Finland.
It feels like it but it's not.
Okay.
I really want to get up there.
You know what?
I can.
What am I even doing here?
I have TNT.
Easy mode.
Why am I thinking about this so much?
I was really trying to look for a way up there.
Like so hard and I could just use TNT.
I have to remember this.
Terrain is destructible.
Polymorphine potion?
I am curious about all these different potions.
Like what is the deal with polymorphine?
Like why would I ever want to turn myself into a sheep?
I understand the chaotic one.
Like the reasoning behind wanting to use that but maybe I can mix it somehow.
Oh look at this.
That's for you sir.
Oh shit he's gonna come here isn't he?
That's for you!
This guy is dangerous.
That's right.
You mad bro?
All right let's play this save.
Let's go to save areas with no fire.
Where did he go?
Look at all this fire.
This guy's blowing everything up.
I mean I'm also sort of attributing to that.
Whoa!
I did damage him.
That's a good start.
Sir?
Where the hell is he?
There's health!
Is he down there?
He is.
That's for you sir.
I guess he takes reduced damage from explosions right?
Given who he is.
Maybe not.
He's on fire.
And he's not taking damage it seems.
But then again he's been on fire the entire time.
That's nothing new.
My god man.
Oh if I'm out of range he's not actually gonna do anything.
I can plink away at him.
Oh I'm on fire!
Oh this is the wrong uh shit.
Keybinds.
Turn me into a sheep.
Oh wait I can also go into steam right?
That should work.
Come on.
This guy has some hp down here.
I don't like the spark bolt very much.
I feel like it's too low damage.
I like the uh the green balls you start with.
They're usually very nice.
Let's get in there.
Damn it.
Wait maybe it's easier from the top.
Probably like this.
What?
How am I on fire?
Wait what?
What did I just do?
How did I just catch fire?
I'm so confused.
What the hell?
I need to be careful here.
Wait why is that not breaking the stuff?
That works.
I guess uh steel is not broken by dynamite.
Nice.
150 max health.
This is a great start.
Unfortunately I'm at 29 now and that's bad.
And I don't think I ever killed the guy down here either.
He's still alive.
And we've got a... is that a dude with a wand?
He's dead now.
Oh he's not dead.
Okay okay.
Tell me you're dead.
This guy right here is insane.
Got him.
That was a bit of a risk there.
What a duel though.
There we go.
Wait what is this?
Sand.
Right.
So I have erserkium.
I should be using that if I drink this.
I guess that's better than pouring it on myself actually.
You know just... oh this is like a... oh it's on a timer now.
It's not a percentage.
I wonder if that's because I drank it.
I'm gonna try after this.
I'm gonna try and pour it on myself.
You know what?
That makes a lot of sense.
It's a potion.
What do you do with potions?
You drink them.
You don't pour them on yourself.
Makes a lot of sense.
Let's put this down.
Crap.
All right he did.
Where are the collapsed mines?
Actually I don't want to go there because there's a crazy dude hanging out in the collapsed mines.
Oh look at all this sand.
What the hell?
I'm scared.
What the hell is happening here?
Oh shit.
Oh no!
20 hp.
This one sucks.
I'm blaming it all on the wand.
That's how I rock.
That's how I roll.
Oh there's a bunch of poison over there.
I don't like that.
Let's go right instead.
Health!
Holy shit!
Okay I can't die this run.
This is insane run.
Actually crazy.
Tell me this isn't insane.
Get in there.
Nice.
175 already.
Oh what's happening?
I think it's some fireworks.
Just went off.
So we have a bunch of poison down there.
I don't like that.
So what can I do about it?
What if I... okay.
What if I put this down here?
Whoops!
Right, I hit myself with that.
Let's be careful.
Would be nice if you regenerated while being a sheep.
Probably a bit OP.
I'm thinking World of Warcraft style here.
That's what happens usually when you were polymorph'd.
Okay so the portal is somewhere down.
Let's start heading in that direction.
We could use a little more.
I am squeezing the lemon quite tightly here.
So I don't know if I should try and squeeze it any more already.
Oh my god!
The squeezing.
Hopefully I'm hitting him.
Wait is he fighting that guy?
Sir?
Uh-oh.
This is scary.
Shit.
He's on fire.
Burning hell bitch.
That's right.
He's taking damage.
Very slowly.
He picked up some gold!
Look!
He's drinking the gold!
Oh no wait he died!
Oh it looked like he picked up... okay I see.
Never mind.
I'm confused.
It looked like he was just drinking that gold.
Which doesn't make too much sense you know, but still.
This is a bit scary.
Oh no!
Oh what am I doing?
Sixteen HP.
I don't want to go in that fire.
We're gonna leave that gold nugget.
We're leaving it.
Oh this is the brickwork.
That means we're close.
What happened?
Someone broke a vase.
There's a bit of fire there.
Shit.
Burning hell.
There's the portal.
Come on burn, burn, burn.
I need that gold.
There we go.
Oh look at that down there.
Wait I have another wand.
I forgot about that.
I have the rain stuff.
I forgot about the rain!
Completely forgot about the rain.
What the hell?
Oh I'm cheesing him.
Oh no I'm poisoned!
Okay no no we're fine.
Nine HP.
Oh shit.
We need to make it rain.
Removes the poison.
God that's such a cool spell man.
Look at that.
Make ourselves wet.
Oh that's perfect against this guy, right?
In fact...
Wait did he die?
Wait a minute.
It's fire.
Water is weakness.
Did I just discover something?
Is he?
No wait.
Yeah look!
He died in the water!
Oh there's so much gold though.
Grab the gold.
Okay oh that was fire there.
That's why I took a bit of damage.
300 gold.
Oh man I should go in here.
I should go in here.
Don't be a hero.
Just go in.
Holy crap the guy died in the water.
Let's see what we got.
300 monies?
That's not too bad either.
I like it.
Okay let's see what we have here.
What's this?
Teleport bolt.
A magical bolt that moves you wherever it ends up flying.
Whoa!
Wait really?
Dude that's insane!
Hello?
Is that not immediately crazy to have that?
It's like the opposite of that other spell I found where I brought the enemy to me.
I'm bringing myself to wherever the thing is hitting.
Okay awesome!
And this?
Poland.
Oh I don't want to have that.
In fact I'm fighting Poland hard now in real life.
What is this?
Heavy spread.
Oh that sounds cool.
The rock?
Here's the thing.
I don't... Okay let's check the perks.
I was about to say I don't want the rock unless I can have infinite, right?
More hatred.
More aggressiveness toward each other.
Invisibility.
You're invisible.
Stains, casting spells, kicking and taking damage makes you temporarily... wait permanently?
You gain additional chance to deal critical hits as long as there are enemies near you.
Bro this one sounds insane, does it not?
Wait really?
Okay so I'm I'm revealed now.
How long?
Uh temporarily visible.
Oh stains!
Oh wait I'm stained by blood.
Oh I see.
Okay.
Fucking hell that's awesome.
That seems insane though.
This bouncing... this one.
That's actually an insane spell.
This is my jam.
Oh no wait this is the wrong one.
Oh no I was hoping this would be the big slow ball that moves.
I mistook that for a different one.
Shit.
Sparkbolt with trigger.
I mean I need some damage.
I'm gonna take that.
So sparkbolt with trigger means if that hits here it's gonna release the next one in the line.
So if I do this, if I hit up here now it's gonna release the green.
Watch.
Actually and you know what?
What if I hit an enemy with it?
Will it just release that thing in the enemy's chest?
Meaning it will take full damage from whatever is being released.
Because that would actually be kind of crazy.
Also I have a question now.
If this thing bounces where do I end up if I actually combine this?
Oh wait this is not what I think it does.
This actually shoots this one first and then it does that.
This is a projectile itself.
Never mind.
Okay I was about to check whether or not the teleport happened at the first impact or after the bounce.
But obviously that's not how this works.
So but if you do this for example it may do that right?
But if I hit an enemy with it it will actually do... it will hit twice.
It will hit for this one and that one.
If I'm not mistaken here.
Oh I can actually try that.
There's fish.
Nope!
Oh shit I didn't mean to pick that up.
God damn it.
Whatever.
But yeah look it shot twice.
Oh wait a minute.
Come here.
Ah did it?
I'm not sure now actually.
Yeah I'm not sure now.
What is that sound I'm hearing?
It sounds like someone's is dragging metal across a stone floor.
Let's try pollen.
Obviously I gotta try it.
A small floating projectile that homes towards nearby creatures.
Ooh really?
Well, if it homes, not bad.
It does pretty decent damage.
If I can shoot this around corners, like that.
Oh even better.
Watch.
Shoot around corners?
This is so cool.
Come on.
Are you kidding me?
So then we have this one, blood cloud.
I don't know if I want that.
Because that means I'll be stained.
Right?
And then I'm not invisible.
Let me try this one.
What is this?
Gives the projectile a much lower cast delay.
But no respect to your aim.
Spread plus 720 degrees.
Wait that's more than 360.
How does that even make sense?
Why is it more than 360?
Why does that number go higher than 360?
Unless we're talking in...
No, that's definitely degrees.
That's not radiance or anything.
Also that would be much lower in that case.
Anyway, let's try this.
So it's a modifier.
So if I do this it will modify it.
And it shoots it in a random direction.
That is the most useless shit I've ever seen in my life.
Why would you ever want this?
Unless... Unless...
Uh...
Oh, wait a minute.
Unless...
Let's say you do something like this.
I shoot around a corner.
I hit here.
Right?
It's a trigger.
So it's gonna cast heavy spread on this in a random direction over here.
So let's say this was not a bouncing burst.
But it was something explodey.
Something that explodes a lot.
So you could basically like curve a projectile around a... not curve, curve, but do that.
And look!
You can cause some chaos in another room.
Let's say you have a little opening, like a little crack to look through.
You go and you cause ultimate mayhem in there.
That would be kind of cool.
Uh, right.
Also, let me look at this wand.
So this one has 250 max mana.
This one has 98.
That's not very good, is it?
This one is actually... Oh, this is shuffle, but it's only one anyway.
So it doesn't matter, I guess.
If I do this... Oh yeah, that's good.
That's actually really good.
I like it.
Probably a ways to use the trigger on that.
So rather do that.
That's better.
And then I do need one wand with the TNT, obviously.
We definitely need that.
I'm trying to figure out how I could... So I shoot this.
It's... Oh, wait a minute.
This actually... this could work like this.
Wait a minute.
Oh, watch.
I can teleport around corners.
Damn, that's cool.
How badass is that?
Fuck yeah.
What if I do this then?
This is gonna be chaotic though.
Because this will teleport me randomly in the direction I hit.
This is so much fun.
Holy shit.
Oh man.
Ah, okay.
Cool.
Heavy spread.
Actually, it does...
Recharge.
It does actually reduce recharge time a lot.
So I... yeah, so that's the trade-off, right?
You receive a much lower cast delay and recharge time, but the aim is crap.
So you need to put this on something where aim doesn't matter too much, right?
Like explosives, where you're gonna be out of harm.
So that's how that works.
Now, let's try some of these other ones.
The hollow egg is weird to me.
I'm not maybe I will have a rock.
I mean, I should use my money and maybe I will have a blood cloud.
Ah, wait.
No, no, no.
I think I want to try this for once.
Glittering field.
Oh, dude.
Exactly, exactly.
This.
Shoot around corners and cause mayhem.
Oh, wait, no.
Huh?
Oh, wait, this is a static projectile.
Maybe that's okay.
So the cast another.
Why does that not work?
Huh?
Is it because it's a static projectile and this only works with another projectile?
Huh, that's interesting.
I could have sworn that would work.
Oh, don't use this because I can't refresh spells.
The pollen actually sounds pretty cool as well.
Maybe I will do something like this.
This seems like the white.
Wait, why is it so dude?
This is the ultimate spell.
Oh, wait, I'm running low on manner real quick.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Wait.
Oh, I'm missing two mana.
That's why it didn't work.
Ninety ten.
That's a hundred.
This has ninety eight.
So if I do this, this should work.
Yep.
There it is.
I mean, not that I care about this because this spell right here does actually no friendly fire.
I could just go nuts with that, you know, but then again, it has a certain amount of uses.
So maybe I shouldn't do it.
I think I like this.
Notice also now how fast it shoots.
If I remove this, watch.
And that's only because let's see here.
Point seventeen.
Um, I wonder what's having the most effect.
Is it the cast delay reduction or is it the recharge time?
So the way I understand this, spark bolt with trigger is fired first.
It spells per cast is one, right?
So that means this one is being cast.
Plop.
It hits a wall.
That triggers another spell.
This one.
But that's a modifier.
So that will trigger this spell at the location, right?
But it shoots faster, meaning it starts over.
Okay, so it is the recharge time then because it starts over much faster.
That's the way I have to remember.
This recharge is like the whole thing starting over.
It's like a sequence.
Start over.
I like this spell like this.
This is a sick spell.
And in the second one, I'm gonna have...
Oh, I could also... No, I'm gonna have dynamite here.
And in the third one, let's do...
Dude.
We gotta have a... Dude, I can just switch whenever I want.
Oh, it's a... Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I just took some damage.
Wait, do these damage me?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Good to know.
Paulin is indeed dangerous.
Confirmed.
Let me grab this as well.
And back.
I'm just gonna go, honestly.
Fuck it.
Let's just go.
Yeah.
Oh, but I don't have a straight shooter, do I?
Maybe it is better to do this.
It's safer and I... this is like... I need a straight damage wand.
Oh, actually, do this instead.
Oh, but it's too slow.
Unless... What if I do this?
Oh, but it spreads it everywhere.
Yeah.
Reduces the recharge time, but it's spreading everywhere.
That's terrible.
It's still doing it.
Oh, you know what?
I should be using the board over here to understand what's happening.
Okay.
Yeah.
Just do...
Oh, I don't know, man.
This is a damaging wand.
Like, it shoots decently fast for now.
And we're probably gonna find more wands.
It's just that this is such a nice, crazy run so far.
Look at all the HP we have, and we have invisibility.
I feel like I should really try and make something great right now.
You know?
The bouncing burst.
I mean, I could do... What if I just go a little nuts?
Wait a minute.
Spells per cast.
Minus... Wait a second.
Maybe that's actually better for a straight damage wand.
I'm gonna use this as my straight damage wand, and this is gonna be my shoot-around corners and do things.
No, you know what?
I'm gonna not do the shoot-around... I'm not gonna be fancy.
Fuck the fanciness.
We're going, uh, this.
We have a teleport, we have a bomb, and we have a damage.
Keep it simple for now.
I can rock with this.
Let's go.
Let's be careful now.
Straight up, there's an enemy.
Good.
Uh, he has a bomb.
Shit.
Yeah, kill yourself.
That's how I like it.
Very good.
I'm afraid... Oh, you know what?
We have the... Oh, we don't have rain cloud anymore, of course.
But dude, we're invisible again.
This is so crazy.
This is like... I can totally scout ahead.
It's like the ultimate safety.
Oh, but I'm not invisible now, because I'm... Dude, that's just not a health here.
Thank you.
I will take that.
Thank you very much.
This is the urn.
Watch.
Also, I'm very stained.
I would like to be in a very hot environment, actually, in this case.
Maybe I will just wait for this to sort of...
How do I get rid of this quick?
Is there a way to, like...
I guess by flying around, it's like airing my clothes, you know?
There we go.
Look at this.
We're invisible now.
How is that not an insanely OP perk?
Am I crazy?
That box is shaking, and that makes me uneasy.
Look, I can totally scout ahead.
He doesn't know I'm here.
Oh!
Oh-ho!
Hold on.
Oh, shit.
I need to ambush him properly here.
Look at that!
And we're like a fucking ninja.
Like an assassin in the shadows.
This guy, this dude's just throwing bombs for no reason.
I'm being a little too passive here.
There we go.
Plop me.
I have been plopped.
Good.
Plop me.
Come on, next.
This is a nice wand.
It's not bad.
It will do the job, you know?
It definitely will.
I'm stained.
I shouldn't be too afraid, honestly, of the stain.
It's just normal noiter when I'm stained.
And I'm pretty much used to normal noiter by now.
Oh, there's a bunch over there.
Holy shit, dude.
I gotta say, the recharge on this wand is not the greatest.
Like, it's pretty slow.
Get that gold.
Okay.
I have to remember, I do have the broken...
Dude, I wonder if there's a way to repair this broken wand.
Maybe if I destroy the wand, I can extract the spell that's in it, which is obviously an arrow right now.
Am I already at the portal?
Holy shit.
Okay.
Awesome.
Also, I should be... So, am I stained if I drink this?
This does not count as staining.
Oh, sick.
Also, I just wasted that.
I should use it when I see enemies, but yeah.
At least that's confirmed now.
What is this?
Your stomach is almost empty.
I don't understand that mechanic.
Plop.
That's a big pool of blood.
And another portal.
Why is this area so easy?
Usually, this is a big one, isn't it?
This burns forever.
Oh, I guess it does, because it's coal.
And we are in the coal pits.
Dude, it's so sneaky being invisible.
I'm getting that feeling again.
I've told you about this before, but when you do something in a video game where everything just sort of almost... Oh, that was the timer.
It just happened.
Hold on.
I gotta take a sip.
Oh, yeah.
That's good.
Anyway, you know that feeling?
Oh, I guess you don't.
It's a very unique thing I have, or issue I have here.
But when I'm exploring in video games like this, and I'm being a little sneaky or something, or I'm explaining... Oh, there's a chest.
Or I'm exploring terrain that I'm not supposed to explore, like going out of bounds and shit.
I feel like I need to take a poop.
Like, it's a weird biological thing with me.
I need to go take a poop, but I'm not getting that now.
But I'm getting little bits of it, you know what I mean?
So TNT, I think I have to blow my way in there.
Let me blow my way in here.
Nice.
What happens if I blow up the chest, though?
Oh, shit.
Oh, how am I gonna do this, probably?
I need to be at a distance.
Oh, okay.
It just gives me what's inside, I guess.
Uh-oh.
I'm scared.
Got him.
Easy money.
Dude, that gave me a lot of money.
279 already.
Not bad.
There's a dude... Oh, someone's throwing things.
Also, I have to remember.
This is insane.
I have to remember to use this in situations where I need to escape.
It's the ultimate ability.
I kind of want to throw this rock in his face.
Oh, come on.
Oh, shit.
He's gonna start spawning shit.
Dude, I can farm infinite money.
If I just kill all the little things, he keeps spawning.
Right?
Not that I want to do that now, but I could.
Because they give money.
That is crazy.
I don't want to chase that gold.
I'm scared.
There's too much goop here.
You know what?
I'm gonna blow this up.
Why does that not get set on fire?
Make me invisible?
Come on.
I need invisibility.
I wonder what determines how this actually disappears.
It's got to be a combination of different things.
Okay, I'm invisible now.
Shit, I thought I made a hole.
I didn't.
There we go.
Let's scout the area.
What if I bump into enemies by accident?
Or on accident?
That is so cool.
I guess I want to take care of the big guy first.
So he doesn't... Oh, he's trapped in there.
Perfect.
Okay, okay then.
Not bad at all.
These things are going to spawn lava when they die.
Fuck, how did I fucking get hit by that?
That's incredible.
I guess I shouldn't be close to them because they will shoot projectiles and instantly hit me if I'm too close.
Better do it from a distance.
Look at that.
That's easy when they're far away.
Just do that.
Uh-oh.
Got him.
There's a lot of money there.
I do want to grab it.
That was a bit risky because there's fire and there's a nuclear device.
Let's go up here.
Can I use the steam to clean myself of status effects?
Ah, maybe not.
I like the sound.
Whoa!
I thought he was aiming for me.
So the issue is he's going to turn around and shoot me instantly.
So I need to be ready.
I have an idea.
Check this out.
Fuck you!
I was trying to kick the stone into him, but he jumped.
That bastard.
There's a wand.
Hold on.
I'm too tempted.
I gotta do this.
Burn it all.
That's so satisfying.
Got him.
He was just about to shoot me, so I shot him.
It's only fair.
Uh-oh.
I bet you that's going to release a shit ton of gold if I actually kill it.
Let me wait for this fire.
What do we got here?
Acid.
Oh, acid ball.
Ah, sure.
I mean, I may as well take it.
I can always replace it later.
Oh, they explode after a certain time.
I didn't realize.
Man, look at all that lava.
Damn!
That one has some HP.
Got him.
No more spawning.
There we go.
Well, don't get hit by that.
Invisible again.
Look at this industrial revolution stuff in the background.
You know what's funny?
When you rise, when you're invisible, you don't have the effect or the sound of going up.
There's a bunch of gold in these hills.
Maybe I want that, actually.
I still have a bunch of bombs, so why should... fuck.
Why shouldn't I?
Right?
Hell yeah.
It's free real estate, as they say.
Thank you.
That was a good amount.
Well, that's a dead end there.
I have to remember, I need to drink the berserkium.
Okay, we've got a portal.
I'm not taking it yet.
I still have a lot of HP to play with.
I'm feeling hella confident, but I'm also being cautious.
What's happening in there?
Why is that... Wait, I'm stuck.
I'm stuck!
Okay, we're right.
It seems like the game sort of auto unstocks you after a while, because I was definitely stuck there.
Maybe the game recognizes that, stays, and it's like, push this character a little bit.
Okay, nothing up there.
We have now explored that region.
What do we have down here?
A dude with dynamite.
There's also a guy with a bomb.
Let me take care of him first.
Stand still.
There.
Fuck you.
I can't believe you hit me in the face.
That's unreal.
You cannot underestimate these enemies, man.
They will fuck you up if you're not careful.
If you look away for a second, they will take advantage of that.
Oh, I need that goal.
Nice.
Keep going.
I want to find secrets.
I want more lore.
You know what?
I'm going to get in there.
Did he just kill his friend?
What happened?
Why was there a corpse?
Sir, you are free.
In fact, that's for you.
Shit.
I'm going to farm gold.
I'm going to let him spawn.
These little things.
Oh, it's actually harder than I thought, because he's going to follow me around, and it's hard to pick up the gold.
Oh, 63.
That's a good amount of gold right there.
Look at that.
Smooth operator.
500 gold, baby.
And still 143 HP.
This is an incredible run.
Don't get hit by the fire.
Grab that gold.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Another portal.
Let's see what's down here.
And whoa, what's happening?
Why there's so many?
But they all lead to the same place.
I think the next part is the snowy area.
There's a guy there.
I kind of want to get to him, but I don't want to use all of my explosives just yet.
Uh, can I go?
Nah, you know what?
Let's just go through.
Hold on.
Acid?
That eats through that shit, no?
Look!
Yeah!
Yeah, dude!
You can dig with this!
Look how it dissolves everything but gray rock.
That's actually such a cool effect.
Can I set this on fire?
It's flammable.
Wait, I know how to do it.
No, I don't know how to do it.
I don't have any flammable things.
Oh, a rain cloud of blood?
Wait a minute, I have a knife.
Oh, I can't use these though.
Of course, I'm an idiot.
I can't use them.
They're not on my wand.
Shit.
That was dumb.
I could go down here, but that... Oh, this is not lava.
This is blood.
Oh, yeah, we're fine.
Uh, what does he have in his hand?
Is that a handgun?
What is he using?
Why didn't he react to me at all?
That's weird.
Very odd.
Oh, it was invisible.
That's probably what that was.
Okay, let's go down here now.
I am clearing this area, dude.
So this is oil.
Gotta be careful here.
Nice.
We got a dude.
I'm super slippery and I'm oily.
Oh, we cannot get hit by that.
That's bad times.
Oh, shit.
Oh, the oil is burning.
Fuck.
Oh, thank God.
That could have been real bad.
Look at this.
All of the oil is going to be gone.
Isn't that cool?
I love little, uh, emergent gameplay stuff like that.
What do we have over here?
Exquisite me?
Oh, I'm gonna fuck that guy up.
Let's be careful.
Yeah, come on.
I know you're mad.
I'm invisible again.
It's so good.
You know what I need with this invisibility?
I need a high impact, projectile, high damage wand.
Something like the sniper that I had in the earlier run.
Remember?
Oh my God.
I could line up the craziest shots.
It would be so crazy.
I can't wait.
We better have a million gold before we go through the portal because we need to purchase as much shit as we can.
Wait, wait, wait.
Drink that potion.
Now we're berserk.
Oh, no.
You hit me.
Let's play safe.
Play safe.
There we go.
We have a couple more.
Good.
Okay, that's scary.
What if I kick it?
Oh, you can totally kick the chain off.
Cool.
Okay, this area is bigger than I thought now.
There's way more here than I thought.
That's going to blow that up.
Yep.
I can't do anything about that lava, unfortunately.
Oh, you know what?
I have an idea.
There's a guy below me.
Watch.
Whoops.
Fucking awesome.
I was going to have it hit here, fall down, and then shoot it mid-air and have it explode on him.
It would have been a cool action movie thing, but unfortunately, it didn't happen.
There we go.
You just get invisible again.
Ah, shit.
I hit the water.
The objects you kick off a cliff, I was about to say, reveal the area for you, so you don't actually need to go there.
You can throw things in and it will reveal it.
That's interesting.
There's a dude down there.
Got it.
Bro, I'm a pro at this game.
Holy shit.
Am I, though?
Or am I just really lucky with my perk?
That's another thing to consider.
It's both, I would say.
Definitely pretty good at this game.
That's a heavy rock.
Look at all that acid.
I've been here.
Oh, there's a bunch of gold here.
I kind of want to blow it up, but I also kind of want to save my bombs.
Yeah, let's save the bombs.
We have three bombs left.
Okay,
just a big vat of water, but there is things on the left here.
Colvane wood.
I'm going to try and dig my way in there, but let me do it from up here.
I wonder if there's fall damage.
Like, if you fall enough of a distance, will you die?
I don't think so.
Okay, there's no way to get in there from up here.
It is down there then.
All right, all right.
Time to do some hole blowing.
Blow some holes in the walls.
Here we go.
I need to be, I need to time this.
It's like worms.
Not bad, not bad.
Let's get a little further away.
Oh, that's perfect.
Oh, lovely stuff.
Hello, what the hell is that?
I'm scared.
Become invisible.
Invisible, invisible.
Oh, okay.
Percircium.
Maximum speed.
Oh, it spews lava, it seems.
Got him.
All righty then.
Sweet.
Hello, the hell are you?
Did I get him?
Oh wait, he's teleporting.
I can do that too.
I can teleport as well, buddy.
You're mad, bro?
Where are you?
I'm invisible now.
He's not dead, he's not dead.
He's somewhere.
Fungal caverns.
Hello.
What is this?
Invisiblium potion.
I don't need that shit.
I am permanently invisible, bitch.
Uh-oh.
I can't hit anything, can I?
What are those things up there?
Oh, they explode.
In slimy goo.
Hopsy daisy.
Where are you gonna appear?
Show thyself?
Okay, we've got little babies of those thingies too here.
I have a feeling those mushrooms are... Oh, we've got ghostbusters.
Oh, he's clearing them, look!
Wait, is he invisible?
Is that little guy invisible?
Who's he shooting at?
I feel like I don't have the weaponry for this, but let's try it anyway.
Yeah, kill enemies for me, dude.
Yeah, look at that, he's clearing things for me.
Thank you.
Fungus.
Okay, fuck it.
I got him.
Come here.
Oh!
Wait, what?
What's happening?
Did I accidentally...
Ah!
We gotta get out of here.
Let this guy deal with each other.
Oh, it's teleportation!
I understand, I understand now.
I know what's happening, I know what's happening.
Yeah, let them kill each other, that's fine.
Yeah, kill him, come on.
Yes, yes.
Shoot him, my boy.
Okay, kill him.
Don't hit that teleportation.
Man, his weapon doesn't do a lot of damage, does he?
That's very terrible.
I'm gonna shoot him though, from here.
Oh, oh no!
We're fucked, we're fucked, we're fucked, we're fucked.
Run!
Holy shit!
Okay.
You bastard, come here.
Come on.
Oh man, I'm squeezing that lemon again.
Oh, I can shoot the projectiles mid-air, that's nice.
Let me get some of that berserkium.
I think we're empty now, we're all out.
But being invisible here is kind of great.
Is this bad for me?
Oh no, this is bad for me though.
I was almost caught in a bad spot.
Oh, there's another one.
Invisible, come on, there we go.
Let me take care of this guy first.
What is this?
Is this...
It's teleportation, I should be careful with that.
That's actually insane.
Oh, it's right there!
It's a duel!
Got him.
God, this one sucks.
But look at me making do with what I have.
Actually really fun.
Why is the thing shaking?
Don't shake.
He has a wand that scares me, because I don't know what that will have.
That could be a crazy wand for all I know.
Also, this guy is hurt.
Look at his blood.
There we go.
Lots of gold for me.
Then we have this dude up here.
I need to be invisible.
There we go.
Take it easy now.
He teleported.
Oh,
he's taking care of the animals.
I can actually see what wand he has, I guess.
Some kind of shitty wand, it looks like.
Oops.
Wait, oh, there's terrain in between us.
He doesn't notice me.
Okay, I have an idea.
Check this out.
Sir, you like wands?
How about this one?
Oh, it shoots random spells every time.
I thought it was arrows.
Never mind.
Nice.
Wait, is this guy my friend?
Why is he... Oh, wait, he died!
He got killed by this fucking ant thingy.
Wait, why... Oh, that guy has HP.
He ain't fucking around.
Look at all the slime coming out of him.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Get some mana.
Holy shit!
My god!
Then we have a horko, I think the name was.
He's sort of wedged in there, that's annoying.
Let's become invisible.
Oh, that's gonna take a while.
There we go.
Give me that.
There's a guy in there, but this also counts as wall, it seems.
He doesn't react to me.
There's a frog.
I'm scared of that.
Kill it.
That's a big frog.
Oh, it has a tongue!
Oh, shit.
Oh, what the fuck?
I've got a mage.
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
I need to see what he does.
This terrain right here is so chaotic, I can't see what's terrain and what's not.
You know what I mean?
I can shoot it away, it seems.
There we go.
Man, he's wedged in there again now, just like the other guy.
What the fuck is happening?
You can barely see a thing?
Stand still, stand still.
Just wait, just wait, just wait, just wait, just wait, just wait.
Oh, this is a terrible debuff.
Wow.
Holy shit, I'm not gonna deal with that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, we're not doing that.
Fuck that.
But I see things down here, I want to get to that somehow.
That is, what is that?
Why can't I see it?
Ambrosia potion?
What the hell is that?
Can I get in there?
I don't have any bombs left, unfortunately.
Oh, but wait, I do have this.
Will that eat its way through?
Yeah, look at that.
Beautiful.
Can I get in?
I can.
Oh, I could have also just used my teleportation wand, actually.
Oh, I'm full.
Throw away that one, it's empty.
Whoa!
Uh, that's not what I meant to do.
Protection from all.
Uh, what?
We're not talking damage immunity, are we?
That would be crazy.
Hold on, I need to empty this.
That seems a little nuts.
Oh!
Dude, I got turned into this exactly when I saw this enemy down here.
I didn't even notice him.
So I thought he attacked me and I died or something.
That was such a jump scare.
Holy fuck.
Throw that away.
There we go, it's empty.
And now we do this.
Give me all this stuff.
Uh oh.
Not now, not now.
There's an enemy on the right.
Is that the dude that turned me into someone that couldn't see at all?
I think it's time we head out of here.
Call me crazy, but oh, okay.
He's down there now.
In fact, I do want to kill him.
I do want to kill this guy.
Let's murder him.
Come on.
Is that the same guy I damaged a lot earlier and he never died?
So look at this, this is all cool.
I should be able to get to this gold using this.
Oh my god, that's awesome.
Oh wait, I think it's dissolving the gold.
Unless I'm crazy.
Sir, come here.
You know what?
We go somewhere else.
I don't have the guts.
I'm sorry.
I'm too much of a pussy.
We have a thousand gold.
It's time to leave.
Play it safe, dude.
Play it safe.
Oh yeah.
Someone's shooting.
I can hear it in the distance.
Wait, why the 220?
I don't understand that.
Wasn't our maximum health 175 before?
And it increased our health by 10?
What?
What the hell is this?
Trigger?
What is that?
Oh dude, I have a thousand.
I can pretty much buy all of it.
Almost.
Four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Yeah, almost all of it.
Ooh, these ones I like, I think.
I like the... That's a fire trail?
These are good.
Hold on, let me see the perks.
Perks, perks, perks.
Feared by worms.
Worms run away from you and worm and luki enemies no longer destroy terrain while burrowing.
Huh.
All right.
Bombs materialized.
Bomb-like spells can be placed in the item space in inventory and used like throwable items.
Holy shit, okay.
More blood.
Nah, I don't want that.
You know what?
I'm gonna do this.
Faster projectiles.
You protect how spells fly faster than before.
You take no direct damage from explosions?
You bleed flammable oil, but are immune to fire?
Whoa, hold on now.
I... dude.
Wait, you take no direct damage from explosions?
So does that mean if I'm not like hit by an explosion directly on my body, I won't take...
I will take damage, but if I take damage from the AOE, I will take damage?
Is that no...
That would be stupid, right?
Okay, so this one is kind of a catch-all because you also bleed flammable oil.
But then again, that's only good for me because everything is...
I think I need to try this, dude.
But this one also sounds good, doesn't it?
With all the fucking explosions in this game, we gotta have explosion immunity.
What?
Okay, so let me actually look at the wand stats.
So, okay.
Okay.
I'm looking for something with this very low recharge time.
Look at this one.
This sucks.
Three seconds almost.
This one has 0.3 seconds.
And it also has the digging thing.
So let me see what this is.
Oh, the chainsaw, right.
A good tool for cutting meat.
Also has some magical properties.
Right!
I did experiment with this a bit.
How does that work again?
Sparkly bounce.
I know that one.
Triple scatter spell.
Right.
It increases spread by... So this is like that one, but to a lesser degree, I guess.
Ah, it's not quite the same.
This one reduces recharge times, too.
But it's like similar... No, this is a multicast.
This is a projectile modifier.
Right.
So this is actually going to modify the next one in the sequence.
Whatever that is.
And if that next one in the sequence is a multicast, then, and get this, three spells are going to hit.
And when they do hit, they're all going to trigger heavy spread.
Right?
That's the way I understand that.
That seems insane.
So if I were to do, let's say this one, actually do this.
Where's this one?
So this is a trigger.
Let's say it hits a surface.
But then I do this.
Oh, but then I need three spells.
Wait a minute.
Let me get some spells.
We can get this one.
It's cheap.
Ah, wait a minute.
What if I stack triggers?
We got to try this.
What if we stack triggers?
That's another question.
Trigger on trigger on trigger.
Bifurcated.
So let's say we do, actually forget that for a second.
Let's just do this.
So basically what's going to, wait, wait, wait.
No, this one away.
This one.
Modifier.
No, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
What am I trying to do here?
I forgot what I was trying to do.
I was going to add the heavy spread to all three of these.
Yeah, so this is right.
So this is a projectile modifier.
It modifies a projectile.
What comes next?
It's not a projectile, but it's a multicast.
Off projectile.
So this is one big batch.
This is a batch projectile that's being modified with the heavy spread.
So watch.
This is gonna shoot three spells now with low accuracy.
And wait, hold on.
Yeah.
And those three, and all three of those spells.
Oh, oh, oh, it's just going to modify the direction though.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, I don't, okay, I don't understand this at all now.
Huh?
Wait a second.
Okay.
Oh, it's shuffling.
Fucking hell.
That's what's happening.
My goodness.
I was so confused.
So if, okay.
Oh, so then I can't actually, oh, wait, we do have more ones though.
Uh, this is a no.
So let's hold on.
Oh God.
Let's, uh, put this here for now.
I put it here.
Let's get rid of the shitty one.
Then I don't want, I don't want that.
Fuck no.
Change that out.
And then we do this again.
Now watch.
So it,
oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It does exactly what I think it does.
Wait, uh, if, if I click once, but it's only shooting one spell.
Am I crazy?
Okay.
I'm not understanding this.
Maybe it's the triggers that are messing with me right now.
Let me try and change that out with something else.
Put, uh, I don't even, I don't even know.
Do I just have a normal, let's buy this one as well, by the way.
Put it here.
I love this effect.
Okay.
So let's do this for now.
So fireball is also a nice spell.
Oh, I just, right.
Just leave that there for now.
That's fine.
Uh, so wait, let me do, let me try this one.
So what's the difference?
0.05, 1.08.
0.05.
I don't understand how this works.
It's not doing what I think it should do.
So the way I understand this, I am, I want to shoot three spells, right?
Uno dos tres, these three, they are being all cast at the same time with low accuracy.
And this whole batch of three spells being cast at the same time with low accuracy is being modified by this.
Right?
Meaning all those three spells being cast with low accuracy are now being cast with terrible accuracy.
Oh wait, that is what's happening.
Oh yeah, that is what's happening actually.
Look.
Wait, is it shooting two of the...
Hmm, let's do one of each.
So if we see all three now, we know.
Okay, that's how it works.
Thank God I was losing my mind.
Okay, good.
I already have a bunch of shit up here.
So the chainsaw, a good tool for cutting meat, also has some magical properties.
Recharge time minus 0.17, but it increases spread.
Wait, speed?
Okay, I don't know what speed means in this case.
But if I, okay, so if this is a, it's a protectile.
Right.
Oh, that's right.
It did increase cast speed, didn't it?
I remember this now.
So if I do that and I do this, look how slow it is.
Uh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
I need this one for that because it casts three spells per cast.
So put these out here for now.
This is a mess.
So if I now do that with this, so now we have three spells, projectile, projectile, projectile.
I don't understand why this is a projectile.
It's not going anywhere.
Bop, bop, bop, bop.
Okay.
Oh, wait a minute, actually.
Give me a more.
This is a mess.
I don't want the trigger.
It's messing up my testing.
Like a lot.
And I'm running out of space for these things.
Let's just put these here for now.
Uh, this one.
So now it
shoots all of these three at the same time.
Watch.
Pum, pum, pum.
But if I remove this,
much slower.
So if I have a wand that has more spells per cast as a stat, it's worth it to throw this one in.
It's like a little extra speed on top, you know?
You can speed it up a bit.
Which is nice.
Uh, so that's that.
It's like a, it's basically a stat modifier if you think about it.
It takes up a slot, but it also modifies stats in some way.
It increases spread fine, but it also reduces recharge time.
Not bad at all.
Okay.
Now, can I make a crazy wand out of this here?
Out of any of these things.
Oh, I have no money left.
Holy shit.
I used all my money.
Whoops.
I need a, okay, this is fine.
Grab that.
Bifurcated.
I think I just want to stick.
Man, I don't have many good wands here.
This is all crap wands.
Actually, this one is pretty good.
Let's do that.
That.
So what, if I stack these two, what does that actually do?
That makes sense.
Actually, that makes a lot of sense.
So it's, it's triggers there.
What is being triggered?
Another trigger that shoots.
And when that triggers, the last bell is being sent.
Very cool.
So if I, what if I do this?
It's much faster.
I hit that thing.
So it's alternating between two trigger and normal, trigger normal, two trigger normal trigger.
So it's, it's going trigger normal.
Wait, wait, what?
Hold on.
Let me see this one.
Trigger normal.
Oh, it's only one spell per cast.
That makes sense.
Okay.
So it shoots this, right?
It triggers that.
That's why we see trigger normal.
Bam.
But the next time I click, it's using this one, right?
But look, that one.
But then it goes trigger, trigger normal, which means it's wrapping around, right?
And it's going trigger, trigger normal.
So this one, and we get three spells because two of them are triggers because this has spells per cast one, right?
So we shoot, trigger.
It triggers another trigger, which triggers that one.
But why is it so much faster?
That's what I don't understand.
What if I do this?
That's also, so let me see if I can predict this.
It's first going to shoot one.
That's it.
It's just one bolt.
Next, it's going to shoot a bolt that has a trigger that triggers another trigger, which then triggers that.
So it's actually the exact same thing.
Oh, it's almost the same thing.
This one has, it's actually a little less good.
This is like the best.
But honestly, it's not better than just this.
That is still the best wand I have.
Am I crazy?
Unless I can somehow play with that.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
If I do this and then I do, what's a good one?
In fact, can I increase the speed of
just...
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Oh, okay.
It is actually, look at the wand.
It is lighting up with the chainsaw.
It's basically yeah, it's just stacking speed.
Yeah, it's just stacking speed.
0.45, 0.17.
Yeah, but it's not better than just this one.
It's insane.
It's actually just the best.
Although this one does three damage and this one does also three actually.
Oh, whoa, wait, what?
Oh, wait, this one adds castellae.
It has an inherent castellae added on top of it.
Oh, fuck, I didn't even look at this.
The spells themselves, of course, like this, the projectiles also have this.
This one reduces the castellae.
It's a much faster spell.
So now it's slow, right?
Watch.
How fast can we make it?
Oh, fuck yeah.
But wait, wait, wait.
Can we, can we make it better?
Can we make it, makes the projectile release damaging sparks as it bounces?
Does that, does that happen on every bounce?
Oh, I like it.
What if we do this?
Oh, wait, this is only affecting the chainsaw right now.
It's not actually affecting the bouncing burst.
What if I do this then?
It's like, oh, dude, I'm blocking.
Normally this would damage me, but I have this.
Fuck yeah.
That's so good.
So wait, this is slower now, right?
But this is faster.
Why is that faster?
That's what I don't understand.
So hold on, I shoot one.
It's explosive that.
Oh, it's actually the same every... So this one is basically just a passive modifier being in here.
That's how that works.
Like it is, I think it is shooting that.
For some reason it's just not appearing up there.
Why is that not appearing up there?
Okay, so this has 0.17 cast delay.
This one has a much lower one.
If I can, I can probably make some crazy shit with this one then.
If I can cram as much shit as I possibly can into all these slots, the better.
And notice, spells per cast is three, so we can do some stuff here.
Let's say I now use this base, but instead of...
No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh yeah, I can add two of these then, I guess, and that's gonna help.
Okay, but it's still a little bit slower because the inherent recharge time is much higher here.
But with this, what if I do something like that?
Oh, wait, wait, what?
Oh, wrong one.
Oh, wait, that's randomized.
Of course, it's a random direction.
So this modifies... What if I put it at the end?
I don't know what's happening, but I love it.
The reason I put it at the end is because I don't want this to modify this projectile before it's fired.
I sort of want the stat of it without modifying the projectile.
So let me understand why it's still being scattered, though.
Let's do one shot.
It's doing that, so bop, bop, bop, bop.
And that makes sense.
Wait, why does that make sense?
It only casts three spells per cast.
It should only do bop, bop, bop.
Oh, no, no, this is not a spell.
It's a modifier.
It makes total sense.
So it's like, this is one spell.
This is number two spell.
This is number three, both of these.
This is a batch.
I need to think in batches here.
Okay, gotcha.
And the next one?
Okay, so that's the first.
The next one is... Oh, wait, no, no, I actually wanted it to do like this.
Is that the same?
It's doing that?
Ah.
So it... three spells.
That's one sequence.
It restarts with a recharge time of 1.08.
Oh, no, wait, it doesn't.
It continues.
It shoots this one.
But because this is a modifier, and it's not... So this is not the end of the sequence, really.
Because it wraps around, right?
It uses this.
It goes a-brup.
And then it says, oh, what am I modifying?
Oh, I'm modifying this one?
Okay.
But it's shooting three spells per cast, right?
So we have to...
do three.
Three again.
So this is not a spell.
This is a spell.
So that's why it's doing all of this again!
And then when it's done with that... Wait, am I just looping?
Am I... Wait a fucking second.
Have I found a bit of an exploit here?
I feel like I sort of circumvented the recharge time.
I feel like I'm constantly looping around without ever triggering a new sequence.
Because look, one spell, two spell, three spell.
Next cast, no spell, one spell, two spell, three spell.
Next cast, but it's not a cast.
One spell, two spell, three spell.
And we keep going.
It's... we go round and round.
I'm thinking of Jim Carrey now from the Truman Show sitting there in the car, but that's what's happening.
Can I make it even more crazy?
Triple Scatter spell.
If I now... Okay, whoa, wait a minute.
If I now put this in to affect the bouncing burst.
Okay, so this is a multi... Does this count as a spell?
Let's just see what happens.
Wait.
So this one right now is affecting this one, that one, and this one.
That's not what I want.
I think I want this instead.
Because one spell, two spell.
Oh, no, no, no, no, wait, this doesn't make any sense.
For this one to make sense, I need to have three different actual spells next to each other.
Yeah, never mind, never mind.
But this is actually insanity.
Oh, like I could, I guess, do this and because I have an extra spell.
Oh, no, I need an extra slot then.
Fuck, I can't do that.
Dude, this is insane.
With explosion immunity?
Watch this wand.
How is that not crazy?
I'm gonna take teleportation on this one.
Uh, put it here.
That's my teleportation keybind.
This is gonna be my first.
And on the third one...
What am I gonna do on the third one?
That's the question now.
Uh, a powerful exp... Does this actually remove environments?
Oh, I guess TNT, of course.
TNT would be the way to go here.
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
What if we... What is the issue with the TNT?
Oh my god, I'm a genius.
The issue is we have to time it, right, until it explodes.
So if you want to blow up a wall, we have to be sort of a distance away and shoot it so that it explodes right at the wall.
If I instead do this... Oh, no, wait, then it's just gonna trigger the TNT from that location and it's still gonna have a delay though.
Uh, unless is there a way to circumvent that somehow?
Summons an otherwise empty egg that casts a spell upon cracking open.
Littering... Wait a minute.
Hold on.
No, this is not good.
This is not good.
No, no, no.
Leave, leave, leave that as it is.
It's an insane combination that we have here.
Uh, I kind of want to play with this one, honestly.
What... Okay, what if we just try this?
I... Oh, you know what?
Fuck the pollen.
I hate it.
I hate the pollen.
Question though, do I want this or do I want the spark bolt?
Because this one bounces everywhere.
And maybe that's a good thing because I can't take damage from explosion, right?
Let me try this.
No, no, I don't want that because this has a much larger castellae.
Yeah, that was the reason why I picked this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's an insane want.
It's an insane want now.
The only issue, of course, is that it's a little, uh, you know, inaccurate.
And it will fuck me up, I guess, if I get near... Oh no, I won't get fucked up because I have explosion immunity.
I need to fucking get that out of my mind.
All right, teleportation.
Dynamite.
I think I am ready, dude.
This is pretty much all I need.
I will get rid of some of this shit.
I don't need it.
I don't like that.
I don't need another... Oh, you... Wait a minute.
We could have light on this one.
Hey!
Yes!
Totally!
Yes, let's go for some light as well!
It's a modifier!
Haha!
Yeah, awesome.
Okay, I think I'm good.
I should put something in here, though.
It'll be a waste not to, right?
Let's put some water.
I like water.
Yeah, we can definitely use water.
Let's... Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa there.
We need to click on a certain thing over here first.
Let's calm down a bit.
Yikes.
Picked up the spell refresher.
Now we have a bunch of TNT.
Look, unless... Why did...
Wait a minute.
No, just go.
Let's just fucking go, man.
I'm too hyped.
We gotta go, we gotta go.
I love that thing.
I love it so much, I made it into the thumbnail on YouTube.
The snowy depths.
A very difficult and challenging area.
And look at that.
I wonder if I can pick this up without getting... What the hell is that?
Dude.
Hello?
That's insane.
That is an insane, insane spell?
Hello?
Hold on a second.
Can I... If I can blow up that shit up there, I can still do this.
Oh wait, I'm an idiot.
I can teleport.
Fuck me.
Okay, can I blow this up?
Yeah.
No wait, I can't.
Oh wait, I can.
I can.
Yeah.
I'm still gonna be afraid of explosions.
I can't shake that.
I'm sorry.
Oh!
Okay, you see, that just saved my ass.
Stop hitting the ledge.
What is it hitting?
Okay, there we go.
This is such a waste.
Oh no, I can't.
Wait, maybe I need to be all the way to the left.
Hold on.
I thought for sure I could go back and just do this again.
Damn it.
Anyway, this is insane.
Yeah.
Also, how's the wand?
Actually, decent I guess.
But what does it do even?
I didn't even look really.
So it doesn't really do much.
It doesn't do anything right now because it doesn't have any damage on it.
It's just sort of a bullshit wand.
Okay, are you ready?
Watch this.
Oh wait, I guess it's not very accurate.
You still have to aim it.
But I can bounce it off the wall here so I can do something like this.
Oh my god, this guy is protected by this little thingy, isn't he?
Is that thing explosion immune?
Oh, this is terrible.
Okay, I thought this was way better than it was.
Yeah, I expected more of this.
Come on, bounce!
Oh man, and it also has low mana.
Oh, it is terrible.
Oh, wait a minute.
It's because he's in water, isn't it?
Oh no, it's oil.
Why doesn't that explode?
Hello.
It's a terrible wand.
I've made a huge mistake.
It's all ogre.
How are you not dead?
Jesus.
Like, am I ins... like, what's happening?
This wand sucks dick.
Please let that be an insane wand.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, the accuracy is total utter crap.
Fuck.
Guys, this run is over.
I fucked up bad.
I thought I made a great wand.
It turned out to be crap.
You can't hit anything with this.
I can't hit that guy.
I can't.
Give me this.
What is it?
Uh... fuck, I don't know, man.
Listen, home... no, I don't need any of that.
We gotta find the portal and we gotta get the fuck out of here.
That's the new plan.
We are invisible.
We're gonna have a stealth mission.
Stealth mission activated.
Try to find a wand that doesn't suck.
We will not engage in any combat.
This is some stealth shit now.
In fact, we can still pick up some money here and there.
Oh, shit, what?
Oh, they're shooting at other things.
Come on, what are you shooting at?
Don't, don't, don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot.
Also, I can be revealed by accident here if I hit some kind of stain.
Shit, I can't get through here.
Hmm... I could blow it up.
Crap cake.
We gotta find a portal.
We can't linger in here.
It's just, it's sad, but we do need to find some money though, otherwise it, it is a little bit sad.
Wait, what's happening?
Hello.
Here we go.
What the hell is that?
Venomous curse.
Imbuse a projectile with a curse that makes the target hit by the projectile to waste away?
To, oh, like a poison effect, I guess.
Okay, we gotta try that.
Let's try it with this one for now.
I may have to come back to that shitty one at some point, but let's try it.
Oh, wait, wait, it's not doing it.
Oh, no!
It doesn't shoot.
Huh?
I don't know what's happening right now.
After a period of time, you'll be turned to...
Oh!
I see.
Nope, we're leaving.
There's another wand.
Don't hit me.
Go invisible!
Oh, I'm stained.
That's why.
Oh, this is a disaster, boys.
It's all over.
Let's fucking run.
Oh, my.
The only, I mean, the thing I have is I can go invisible and I can teleport.
I do have a lot of survivability.
That's something to keep in mind.
Leave me alone.
There we go, invisible.
Okay, calm down.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Let them kill each other and find that wand again.
Shit, I'm stained.
Did that guy pick up my wand?
That looks like a crazy wand as well.
I want it.
Uh, I may have to kill him.
I'm gonna do something crazy.
I'm gonna go close quarter and just mash this button now.
Yes!
What do we got?
Lightning bolt, double scatter.
Sure.
Let's put it on...
this one.
I don't want that wand.
So, the question is, do I take damage from this?
Does this count as an explosion?
Does it say blocked at any time?
151 HP?
Let's try it.
Let's go really close.
Yeah!
It works.
Okay.
So, it does have a short range, but how much damage does it do?
Oh, I can't We're back, boys.
The run is real.
That was 150 damage.
How much does it...
125?
Oh my god.
But it shoots with low accuracy, but it doesn't matter, I guess.
Whoa!
I'm stuck!
Oh my go... Okay.
So, you can only shoot a couple at a time.
It's not...
Jesus!
Yeah.
See, snipers are a problem, because I need to get close.
Oh my god!
Yeah, I love this spell.
I love this spell.
Oh, yeah.
We are so back.
We blow that up.
Explosion immunity has never come in more handy right now.
This is so satisfying.
What a cool effect as well.
Just a bolt of lightning exploding in the most hardcore way imaginable.
Look at that.
I just blow my way through things.
Why is there so much flammable gas?
Release the gas!
Oh, I can't.
Wait.
I can't.
Release the gas!
Yeah!
Load up!
Look at that.
Fucking physics.
Insane.
Insano style is what that is.
Wait a minute.
There's something up here.
There is not.
Unless...
Yeah, wait.
We're gonna blow our way through.
No, we can't.
Okay, never mind.
I thought I was damaging it, but I can damage this.
God, I love this wand.
My new best friend.
You know what the best part is?
I can go invisible, go up real close and just go pow!
And they're dead.
It's the most insane build ever.
So watch.
Ninja style engaged.
We're sneaking through the caverns.
Wait, what?
What?
Okay.
Quantum split.
I know about this one.
Uplicate spell.
Electric arc.
Circle of unstable metamorphosis.
Bubbly bounce.
Dude, I know what I'll be doing.
I'll be saving money for this.
Interesting how there's just spells for sale there.
Now the portal was there, but now that I have this wand, I... Bro, I'm not done with this place.
No way, Jose.
Although I am quite low on health, so...
Let's not go too crazy.
But I really want to go crazy.
How does that not blow that ice up?
Another portal?
Make a hole.
So if there's rock, I can't get through, but look at this.
That works.
What do we have in that water?
Whoops.
I do wonder if I jump in water and I use electricity like this, if I'm gonna fuck myself.
Electric damage could still be a thing, I guess.
So I need to sort of be careful, I think.
That is not direct explosion.
So look at this.
I get close.
Actually insane because the invisibility totally circumvents the issue of not having enough range.
They killed both of them?
Wow.
Holy shit!
The damage!
What is this sound?
I'm hearing chains.
Blow up the snowman.
Don't get stained.
We hate stains.
What is that?
Oh, it's a barrel.
Blow it.
Explosions are my friend now.
Oh man, it's so good.
I can't wait to sit and experiment with this electric shit.
Oh!
There we go.
Hey dude.
See ya.
Goddamn.
What is this?
Rusted metal.
The snowman!
The snowman hit.
But yeah.
I'm gonna play some football.
Okay, fuck you.
I was gonna punch it.
Oh, gold just fell on my head.
Dude, what's with the atmospherics right now?
Hello.
Bye-bye.
Dude, I was saved by the bell with this wand right here.
Such an incredible opportunity.
Hello.
Holy shit.
Wait, that guy shoots the same thing.
Is he immune to my spell then?
He's not.
You want to fight, bitch?
But wait, I should be immune to his bullshit then.
Oh my god, I am.
I'm stuck!
I'm sort of immune.
I took a little bit of damage somehow.
I don't know what just happened.
Okay.
At least I know that now.
So here's what I think is going on.
I'm immune to the explosive effect of it.
But if I get hit by electricity somehow, in water or whatever, that's when it's ripped.
And I think that's what just happened there.
I got hit by a little bit of that.
Hapsy!
Wait, did I just block that shot?
The hell?
Unless those shots have a little explosive effect at the end.
That's probably what it was.
That thing is about to explode?
That was cool.
The way it goes...
BAM.
Fuck you.
Oh my god.
Ah, I'm burning!
Okay, thank god.
Burning is still an issue.
We need water.
Oh shit.
Wait, we do have ambrosia polymorphine.
Ah shit.
Right.
Of course that would happen.
That's something I gotta experiment with.
What that defense meant with ambrosia.
Okay.
We have a dude.
We have two dudes.
We can probably one-shot them if we're doing this correctly.
Wait, am I puking?
I am.
How cool is that?
The music activated with my shot.
You hear that ringing?
Is the music actually, like, dynamic?
Notice how certain stems of the track kick in when I do things.
I have not noticed this until now.
Get in there.
There's a wand!
Ah, it's all...
There's rock everywhere here.
I'm not getting in there.
One less.
I do this perfectly.
Yes, that was perfect.
One more.
Shit, we need one more.
Perfect!
That was the last.
Get invisible.
Hold on, we have water on us.
I am nervous.
What the hell is this?
Triplicate bolt.
Uh, let's see here.
Spells per cast three.
Shuffle, yes.
Cast delay...
320 mana max.
Let's try it.
Change it with this one, because it's empty anyway.
Okay, so it's like a mega shotgun.
I mean, it's cool at all, but...
I like this more, you know?
And I do like my bomb.
But, hold on, do I like to want more?
I don't think I do.
It's shuffle, that sucks.
And it also has a long recharge time.
But then again, it does have a bunch of spells available to it, so...
Maybe the recharge time doesn't matter too much in this case, if you have enough spells.
But, I don't want it.
Don't want it.
This is a cool song.
Makes me excited.
Makes me feel a certain way.
So, let me go further up here first.
See what we got.
What we're dealing with.
Dude, I was so...
unsatisfied with that wand I made.
It was such a letdown when I tried it, man.
It looked so cool.
And then it turned out to be a nothing burger.
But then I found this.
The gods above reached down, took my hand and said, child, I know you're suffering, so have this.
And he gave me the power of the thunder.
I am now become soos.
Whoa, that was a sick shot though.
That would have hit me right in the face.
Look at this.
Ho ho!
And it is a double scatter spell, so it will actually do a lot of damage.
What's this?
Homebringer...
Oh, yeah, this is the one I already tried, I think.
No, thanks.
He isn't dead.
Wow.
Wow, wow, wow.
Where'd the gold go?
Did I pick it up?
Maybe I did.
38 HP, that's actually very low.
I think we have to start considering whether or not we should go back.
Find the portal.
Oh, but what is this then?
These powders though.
Brass plus snow pouch.
I really need to find out what the hell that means and how I can use this.
Brass.
So we have chemicals and we have powders.
It's definitely used in some kind of alchemy.
I need to find a cauldron or something.
Maybe that comes later.
And we gotta make something.
We are a fucking mage, right?
Can I make it up here?
Oh, wait, I have a teleport!
I keep forgetting!
Why don't I use it?
Oh, because I will reveal myself.
That's actually a reason why I don't use it.
That's it.
My god.
Does he see me?
What's happening?
Holy shit, holy shit!
Whoa!
Wow!
Calm down!
The hell?
Oh, get fucked!
Yeah, come on then.
Is it a boss?
Holy crap.
Oh, I'm good.
Holy shit, that was scary.
The reason why it was scary, I was sort of stuck in here.
I couldn't go further up.
And this one only explodes after a certain distance.
So I thought I couldn't kill them.
They were too close to me.
I have to remember, I can still use this.
Why don't I use this some more?
I need to get used to it.
I can also fuck with you because it may make you appear somewhere undesirable.
Okay, I'm not getting through there.
You know what?
Let's find a...
Uh, we do have 500 monies.
We needed 600 to buy one of those spells.
But maybe I'll save it for the portal, actually.
I mean, there were some intriguing spells there that I wanted to check.
But...
Wait, have I been here?
Did I explode this already?
I think I did.
Yeah.
You know what?
I think we have to go through.
19 HP, plate safe.
Plate safe, baby.
Just go.
There we go.
229 HP.
What a weird number.
Uh, wow, this is expensive.
I can only afford this.
No, I can barely not afford this, though.
Not that it matters.
Looks kind of shit anyway.
There's a bunch of stuff.
Yeah, I'm taking...
It has my glowing lance.
Three of them.
It's sniper time, baby.
Dude, glowing lance.
Oh, imagine glowing lance with trigger into lightning bolt.
Damage plus?
Hell yeah.
How much, though?
Oh, plus 10.
Yo, that's actually big.
That's big for spells that shoot fast.
Like, let's say a spell does three damage.
That's an extra 10 every time.
Wow.
Not bad at all.
Um, wait a minute.
Before I do that, let's see what perks are in here.
Wand experimenter.
Firing newly found and unmodified wands heals you.
Okay.
You get more critical hits.
When you pick a perk, there's a 50% chance that others won't disappear.
Oh, I think I want this and then I'm gonna hope to get this afterwards.
Let's gamble, baby.
Come on.
Damn it.
So now that is useless unless we make it through this level.
It was a gamble.
We gambled.
It is what it is.
Okay.
I have a bunch of spells here.
Dude, I'm gonna experiment so much right now.
This is gonna be insanity.
This is gonna go insane-o style.
So watch.
Let me see here.
This wand right here is actually a decent wand in itself.
Relatively low.
I mean, okay, so honestly, when you use stuff like Lightning Bolt, you're intending to go close and pop someone, right?
You're not intending to spam it quick, so you don't care about that stuff.
So really what you want is...
What do I want?
This one.
Triple Scatter spell.
Baby.
Wait a minute.
Plus 20 degrees.
Let's see this in action.
I mean, it's hard to see, right?
But that is indeed three of them.
If I only use this one, it only shoots two of them.
Oh my fucking god.
That's why I only did a little damage sometimes.
It alternated, of course, between shooting two and then the next spell...
What just happened there?
There was an enemy.
In my home?
I'm afraid now.
Are you fucking kidding me right now?
This is some insanity.
So watch.
What am I going to do here?
I want to try some crazy stuff.
Buy this.
Replace it with that.
Now with this one...
Oh, wait a minute.
What is this?
Triple Simultaneously Cast 3 spells.
Wait a minute.
Isn't this just a much better version of this?
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Why did the other one feel more accurate?
Am I crazy?
This one is like the same accuracy.
Call me crazy, but I feel like it has longer range as well.
Huh?
Maybe this is even better for me because I wanted to spread out a bit.
In case there's AOE and bunch of enemies, I want them to just get popped.
Right?
So instead of that, let's try this.
Uh...
Baby.
Does that shoot three of them?
Wait, what?
Simultaneously Cast 3 spells.
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Oh, no, no, no.
This is the spell itself.
This is what we have to modify.
So we have to do this.
There we go.
Look, watch now.
Okay, it worked there.
And then it shoots one.
Oh, wait a minute.
Hold on, I'm confused then.
Modify or modify?
I modified this, but this is one batch now, no?
Why does this not...
This...
Oh, it's shuffle!
Oh, that's why.
I'm an idiot.
God damn it.
Okay.
So, you know what?
Uh, new plan.
How about we replace this?
Because I have a feeling that it may not matter too much in which order this is going.
That's...
I'm pulling that out of my ass right now, but let's see.
It does that?
Ah, okay, yeah.
Okay, no, it doesn't matter.
I was...
If I do this though...
No, no, no, no.
Ah, shit.
Dang it.
I mean, you know what?
I could just settle with...
I mean, you don't really need these buffs on the...
You don't need these two on this one.
Honestly, it's overkill.
So, if you do this...
This should shoot three.
What?
Wait a minute.
Huh?
Wait, why doesn't this work?
This should work.
I'm confused.
Simultaneous.
So, it's a multicast.
It's the same as this.
Cost two mana.
30, 30, 30.
So, that's 90 mana.
Oh, it's shuffle.
Fuck, I'm an idiot.
Oh, fuck in hell.
What is actually wrong with me?
Dude, I'm losing my mind.
I'm sorry.
This one does not have shuffle on it.
Fuck in hell.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Throw some shit away.
Give me that.
Give me...
Get rid of that one.
And that one.
My god, I have way too many spells.
Okay, now.
Watch.
That one.
Here.
This will shoot all goddamn three.
Yes!
Good.
Okay.
And then, more damage.
So, we're technically adding 30 damage in total now.
And we're gonna...
Sure, why not.
This should still shoot three.
Yes!
Oh, but the recharge is shit.
Oh, but we reduced recharge.
Wait a minute.
We can do some crazy stuff.
And...
Projecta.
This is insanity now.
Maximum sniper.
Well, what am I limited by?
It's still the recharge time, but...
That is insane.
Oh, oh, but wait a minute.
Oh, wait a second.
If we're limited by recharge...
Can we do something sneaky here?
Can we somehow circumvent the recharge?
Like we did with that other one?
In that case, we need something at the end that will have to utilize...
So, what if I do this?
Oh, but it's gonna start with that, isn't it?
Wait a minute.
Let's say I remove this.
What if I...
So, hold on.
I need another one of these triple spells, basically.
That's what I need.
Oh, what?
Hold on.
Let me see.
Wait, let me see the thing.
Wait, what am I limited by here?
Oh, I think the cast delay is the thing that's limiting it now.
Because look, I removed this.
Oh, never mind.
Okay, I'm not sure then.
I'm not sure.
I mean, not that we need to spam this.
It's just, you know, I'm testing.
It's testing time.
This is great.
Honestly, this is fantastic.
I love that.
I really, really love that.
So, this one, I want there.
Because honestly, this one, I want it to scatter a little bit.
You know?
That's great.
I love scatters.
Okay.
I could also...
Oh, instead of having...
No, the speed is good.
Speed is good.
Although...
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute now!
The trigger is...
Yeah.
Okay, wait a minute.
We can make it even more crazy.
If I...
Hold on, let me see.
It does one.
So, this is one.
It does...
Honestly, actually, it doesn't matter where this is.
It could be here, here, or here.
Because this is all treated as one batch.
Right?
Oh!
Never mind.
Holy shit!
Wait, why does that work?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Wait.
Oh, even better.
Watch.
Uh...
Oh, shit.
I...
Oh, I can hit myself with that.
Huh?
I don't know how I just took damage.
Honestly, I don't understand.
I think I just hit myself with that.
Okay, you know what?
This...
I don't...
So, why does this work this way?
So, it casts one spell.
This is...
This is the spell it casts.
But it shoots three.
So, it shoots all of these at the same time.
This one, when it hits something, it's gonna cast the next spell.
And what is the next spell in the sequence?
Ta-da-da!
It is the triple spell again.
That's why it's so quick.
So, how about...
Because it's so quick now anyway, we removed this and put in some extra mana.
Can we sustain this for longer?
Let me go over here.
Okay, no, it's not worth it.
But it was worth a try.
I mean, you don't need to be spamming this anyway, right?
This is insane as...
Wait, is it bouncing?
Oh, I know how I got damaged then.
This is actually scary.
This one, when it triggers...
When it collides with something, it triggers the next batch, right?
But that triple spell right here is being triggered at the location where it collided.
So, this is scary because if that happens to...
Oh, but how does that hit me?
I guess it's being reflected then.
It's like a reflection.
That's all I have to think about then.
Yeah, look, it's bouncing off and it's like a reflection.
It shoots off in this direction.
So, you know what?
I don't want this.
We're gonna keep it super simple.
This is three as it is.
It's a lot.
It is a lot.
And for that reason, we don't even need this.
We need this.
Yeah, we need that.
Okay, I think we're good.
Now, over here, we can have some fun because we can technically affect this spell, which is essentially one batch now.
We could add more mana because I think that's also what we're limited by here, no?
No, it's the...
It's the re...
Wait, what am I limited by?
Uh, 70...
Oh, super...
210.
Yeah, I'm limited by mana.
I am limited by mana, but I can do this because there's no reason not to.
What?
Dude, I love it.
I love this spell right now.
It's insane.
Ooh, but wait a minute.
Hold on now.
Wait a minute now.
Oh!
I don't know what's happening.
I honestly don't know what's happening.
So it shoots this one, which is one spell, which is all three of these.
They get all shot at the same time, but then this guy hits something.
What does it do?
It shoots the next spell in the batch, which is that one.
Where does it shoot it?
Where it impacts.
So if I hit an enemy with this, that enemy is gonna get fucked, basically.
I think I'll run with this.
This seems fun.
Maybe a little chaotic.
Yeah, you know what?
It's too chaotic.
Let's stick to the basics.
We want to survive.
That comes first.
Then I have the teleport.
Then I have this.
And we're good to go.
Let's fucking go.
We shall move immediately.
There's an enemy.
That's so weird.
Why is it not dying?
Oh, let me try this one.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, that's a lot of gold.
What the fuck?
I was hoping there'd be enough gold for me to purchase something new here.
But alas.
Now, do I want any of these things I threw away?
Maybe.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, I may as well take it, right?
I can throw it away later if I want.
All right, let's keep moving.
Man, this is the first run of today.
What did I tell you?
I am not going to die today.
Cheers to that.
Okay.
Get invisible.
Easy base.
Well, I'm invisible.
So, sir, you like this?
Oh, he became a mist.
Oh, wait, that explodes.
Let's be careful.
Holy shit, that penetrates.
I'm super scared.
I'm going to go invisible.
Watch this.
I'm going to shoot him through the crack.
Give me that money.
Fuck, yeah.
Let me blow that up because I'm scared.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Oh, I take damage from that.
Let's not stand in that.
Can I somehow get rid of it?
Yeah, you can sort of blow it away.
Definitely.
Oh, we've got a dude.
What you want, sir?
Want to fight?
Let me try this weapon on him.
Or let me kill this guy.
Okay, 54 damage.
It's not actually that insane.
I expect...
Wait, why does that only do that?
That should do...
Oh, that makes sense.
35 plus 35 plus 35.
Maybe he has some armor or something.
Definitely the electric shit is better.
Damn, one shot.
Yeah.
Oh, that's a sniper.
I got to be careful of these.
I remember those.
I've had bad experiences with those.
That was a bad time.
What the hell is in that?
Let's have a look-see, shall we?
Oh, lots of fireworks.
Do what a thunk.
I mean, honestly, this weapon right here, it even gets rid of fire.
It's such a violent blast.
It just puts it out.
Love violence.
My favorite thing in the world.
Yo, that's...
That is...
This motherfucker just took the thing.
She's not allowed.
Show yourself.
Oh, wait, I can get in here with my teleport thing.
I see some kind of force field shit right there.
That scares me.
Yo, what's happening?
All right, that's it.
We got to blow it up.
I need to get in there.
What is this man cooking?
Hand it over.
What the fuck is that?
Big magic guard.
Eight guarding lights rotate around you for a time.
Accelerating shot causes a projectile to accelerate as it flies.
Triple spell again.
Man,
I don't know what to...
I think I'll replace this wand.
The TNT is good, but come on.
We got to try this.
How good is this?
Like, what does that mean?
Guarding lights.
How guarding is this?
I guess I need to test.
In fact, I'm just going to activate it before every fight.
I'm not going to intentionally try to take damage with it on because that would be insane.
See ya.
Okay, yeah, it doesn't work against that.
I took damage just then.
Whoa!
Okay, I see now.
They damage enemies.
Holy shit, that's sick.
Spells cast 10?
Hello?
No way.
I'm a melee man now.
Get rid of that.
I fucking love this game.
Have I told you this already or...
Oh, it's not getting rid of that now.
Wait a minute.
Maybe I can...
Cleanse it?
No, okay.
Is there a fire thing on it?
Eight guarding lights.
Sir?
Wait,
where's the gold?
Cough it up, sir.
These are some of the coolest looking explosions I've ever seen in any game.
I shit you not.
They nailed it with the explosions.
It's so...
It's like it's a proper explosion, you know?
It's violent.
It's big.
It's loud.
See ya.
Imagine not having explosive immunity and having this want.
Sounds like a bad time.
Sounds like a real bad...
What is that?
Don't care, don't care.
Just shoot everybody.
The hell is going on in there?
Oh.
They are fighting each other.
Who is that over there?
Wait a minute, can I do this?
Through the wall?
Come here, come here.
I gotta try this through the wall.
Come on, come on.
Oh my god, it actually works.
I'm on fire!
I didn't even notice.
Good thing I paid attention at the very last minute there.
Did you see the electricity sort of cascaded around that metal?
The steel.
Cool effect.
So you don't want to be touching that when this bad boy goes off.
We have this dude down here.
Ah, watch.
Okay, it's not doing super damage, but it's good.
You know, it's still good.
It's this is still the one for me.
I'm gonna wait for all this to blow over.
I'm gonna go the other way.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's okay.
Yeah, blood also conducts electricity.
Note to self.
Don't stand in blood.
Duck, duck, duck, duck.
This one reflects, so...
Oh, nice wand there.
I can just walk through these.
I wonder if they work against enemy projectiles, too.
Can I use these to my...
Let's try it, sir.
I was just about to shoot.
What a mistake that would have been.
If I shoot from now.
Okay, I can shoot from inside of these.
Good, good, good, good.
I got to be careful, though, not to accidentally shoot when they're active.
Can I kick them?
Wow!
I just not think he was going to be able to hit me from there.
That was wrong.
Long range.
This is actually pretty good.
I have to remember, I can do this stuff.
Oh, right, it absorbs in the core.
I was about to teleport to the other side, but then this thing...
It deflected the teleport spell.
Badass.
I hate this freezing vapor.
Can I get rid of that somehow?
Maybe with water, actually.
Yo, what the hell?
What?
I need a rain cloud right now.
Can I electrify this and make it go away?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Dude, I swear the fire is going to get me.
Wait, did I just blow up the spells?
Is that a thing?
Whoops, there's an enemy.
Hopefully, I didn't just fuck up those spells.
Okay, I didn't.
Good stuff.
What is happening here?
Dude, speaking of chests, wasn't there a chest earlier on that I completely forgot about?
Wait, what's happening here?
Did you see that just there?
Things are popping off in this place.
Get rid of this fire already.
I need to fill my potion with water.
If I see water again, I'm going to fill it.
Oh, this guy.
It's so good.
$4.95 money as well, not bad.
Why is there so much blood?
I didn't take blood, blood, blood.
Oh, you know what?
I could pick that up with my bottle.
That would not be too bad.
Let's do that.
Oh, gotta take care of the enemies first.
Let me snipe you.
Just because I can.
Collect it all.
All the oils of blood all belong to me.
Yeah, all the guts and all the blood.
Drink it up.
Yeah.
Yellow.
This game is the best.
Oh, that thing right there scares me.
Let's see if we can't blow that up.
I think I just electrocuted him via this metal.
Maybe.
Does that take damage from freezing vapor?
It sure seems it doesn't.
Come on.
There we go.
Cool effect how the gold sort of pops out of the inside of it, you know?
It splits open in half and the gold just plops out.
Come on.
There we go.
Next, let me slice you in half.
You want some of this?
Yeah.
Very nice.
Dude, I'm owning.
I'm owning, actually.
Legit ownage right here.
Okay, this is a bit too close to comfort that thing up there.
So what I'm going to do is this.
Nice.
All right.
Guess I'm not going that way anyway.
Yo, what's this?
A lab?
Whoa, that was close.
I wonder how much damage that does if I got hit by that point blank there.
Probably wouldn't have been good for my health, I assume.
I do 300 something damage to these guys.
It's wild.
Hey, that thing's going to blow up now too.
Watch.
He's going to get fucked.
Or is it going to blow up?
Sliced and diced.
Yeah, don't even risk it with the fire, honestly.
Fire is the worst thing in the whole world.
Load that up.
The reason I'm blowing these up is because I'm scared of an enemy blowing it up.
When I retreat or something.
May as well get rid of the danger, you know?
We've got to want bombs.
Chaotic transmutation transmutes various liquids and powdery substances within a projectiles range into something else.
That sounds awesome.
Dude, there's so many things out and these are just bombs.
God damn.
Ah, man.
I'm not going to take it.
I like my once right now too much.
Oh no, I'm fire.
I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay.
Oh, wrong spell.
Shit.
I didn't mean to cast that.
Okay, we got to play this safe.
We are at 100 HP now.
What's this?
Polymorphine?
Don't want it.
I will blow it up though.
Yo, this thing just... Oh, all right.
Of course.
I'm an idiot.
Obviously that would happen.
This thing cuts through steel.
My sniper rifle here.
Watch.
That straight up cuts through steel.
That is wild.
Right?
How cool is that?
Oh, this is going to be great.
Watch this shit.
I'm invisible.
Hey, boys.
I need to wait for them to clump up completely.
Here we go.
Oh my God.
Okay, I expected a bigger explosion there, but that's fine.
One guide out.
This weapon is sick.
Look how good it is.
The sniper rifle is a success.
All the money.
All that money.
HP.
Hey.
Yeah, 255, baby.
254.
So weird that it's 254 and not, I don't know, 250.
It is a bit odd, isn't it?
Is this a bit?
The hell is this?
Slice it and dice it.
The fact that this works is insane.
How cool is this game, dude?
Like I sliced through the bed frame and it cuts off exactly how you would expect it.
So goddamn cool.
Wait, did I disable it?
Uh, I'm actually, this is a bit of a scary situation.
I'm in here.
There we go.
Don't even want the money.
So watch, I can get in here because I can slice through steel.
In fact, I'm going to slice a path through it and shoot this guy through it.
Watch.
That is insane.
Oh, I love this game.
Fuck, that is so cool.
What the fuck, man?
That is so fucking cool.
Make a path, make a path.
Look at that.
Oh, there's a guy there too.
Watch through the snow.
Oh, shit.
Yo.
I want to get below here.
Let's go down here.
I have two of the coolest wands ever right now.
Down with it.
And slice it.
In fact, I'm going to name these wands.
I will call this wand the, well, the slicer.
This one up here is going to be the dicer.
It turns enemies into cubes.
Whereas this one turns them into slices.
Dude, they are pets.
They have a whole headquarter here.
Well, I guess so.
It's like Heezy... whatever.
It's about the name.
Heezy base or something.
I'm infiltrating their actual home.
I am a ninja.
Invisible ninja.
Watch this.
I can just kill him through the thing.
Hey.
Damn, look at the strength of it.
I wonder if that's because of the speed up.
Is that what's making this penetrate through?
That would be amazing if that's actually the case.
Can I do anything with these?
Can I sleep in the beds?
Yo.
Okay.
Okay, sir.
Let's let's be in.
Oh, I can't go invisible yet.
Where was this guy?
Hey, sir.
Show thyself.
You were down there, it seems.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye now.
96 HP.
This is getting a little too close.
I don't think I ever made it through this part.
I guess we gotta go down.
Find a portal.
Go invisible.
There we go.
What the hell is this?
Some kind of machine of sorts.
So what are they doing here in this place?
That's what I wonder.
Sir, that's for you.
Here.
Have it.
There it is.
I hit it.
Yo.
They died.
They all died.
They all fucking... What's this?
Blood plus Ambrosia.
Let me drink it.
Wait, what?
Nothing happens when I drink it.
All right.
Oh, don't go down there.
That was close.
Holy fucking shit.
Yeah, so the portal is there, but there's a bunch of shit.
If we can get water down there, we can slowly turn it.
So we need to find some water.
Or just hold on.
Can I blood this shit?
What will happen if I throw blood in here?
Ah, it's going to take forever.
No way.
Unless... Hold on.
Unless I can drain it.
No, it's going to be that weird brickwork, isn't it?
It's going to be very resistant to damage.
Let's find another portal.
There's multiple.
There always is.
Uh...
Cut through here.
It's a little inefficient, but
I'm a little lazy right now.
And then I can do this.
Oh, dude, I only need to cut a small... Oh my god.
Watch this, dude.
Watch this.
Holy shit.
I have the craziest one combination in history.
Oh, I need to clean my glasses.
They're dirty as fuck.
How cool is that, man?
This game is somehow getting cooler every single second.
Okay, we've got enemies.
Oh, here we go.
Yeah, I can shoot through walls, man.
What do you want?
You mad?
You mad, bruh?
I bet you're real mad.
That's right.
Give me that goal.
Actually, don't give me that goal, because there's a fire and I'm afraid.
Uh, okay, it doesn't go that far.
Let's not be too ambitious here.
It does sort of penetrate the steel from a long distance as well.
Incredible.
Incredible weapon.
Oh, what the hell was that?
Wait, does he have that same thingy?
Uh-oh.
Is that gonna be reflecting on me?
Okay, it's not.
It's not.
Okay.
I need to test though.
I'm not entirely sure.
That looks like a mobile version of that reflecting static defense.
There we go.
Oh, he's alive.
Oh my god, look at all the gold!
I can't believe I realized this late that this thing was cutting through everything.
That thing's gonna explode, I'm scared.
Yeah, get in the steam.
I need to blow it up.
Whoa!
Almost a mistake.
Let's just wait for all this to blow over.
Hmm.
Why is there like a vat of oil there?
That's suspicious to me.
Also, there's a guy on the other side.
Oh, you know what?
Oh wait, I need to...
Health.
Health, baby.
Yeah!
That's the best.
Man, floor is slippery because of all the oil.
I need to...
blood it up, I think.
Can I get rid of that fire?
Hold on.
Oh no, that made it worse.
Stupid idea.
Let's just wait a bit here.
Invisible now.
The way it slices through enemies is delightful.
Oh, I have another...
How do you see me?
I was invisible, was it not?
Shit, we lost a bunch of HP.
This can end at any second.
I need to go down.
I need to find that portal.
Get invisible.
Get the fuck out of here.
We have a lot of money.
We gotta go.
How do I get rid of the blood?
Quick, come on.
Drain off.
Oh, don't hit the box!
Whew!
Okay, there's this.
Oh, hello.
Whoa, that was a cool explosion.
God damn.
Love that.
There we go.
Playing it so safe right now.
Hello.
Trying to get up through there, huh?
Portal!
Portal spotted!
I think it's time.
So get the fuck out of here, unless we be extra greedy.
Do we... are we gonna be extra greedy?
I just want to see what's over here real quick.
60 HP is still 60 HP.
60 HP is still 60.
There's a machine over there.
Oh, it's not.
It's one of those.
Okay.
Oh, what do we have?
Is this a dumb idea what I'm doing?
Another portal.
The game is really telling me, okay dude, you gotta go now.
Here's another one.
Please go.
I'm like, I don't know.
What about up here?
You know, you're gonna really take a look around and see if there's anything.
Uh, what's that?
That scared me a little bit.
What just flew around there?
Uh, what the hell is that?
It looks like an enemy on a kangaroo thingy.
That is so odd.
I just killed two enemies with one shot.
Yo.
Okay.
Did he just spawn that guy?
Uh-oh.
This may be a bad idea.
He's spawning them.
Yeah, okay.
We're leaving.
Fuck this.
Or wait, are we leaving though?
What if he shoots me?
Oh, nice.
Fuck you.
Okay, okay.
I'm gonna go.
Fuck it.
All right.
Let's go, baby.
Let's go.
290.
That's a lot of HP, baby.
What do we got?
Oh, I'm rich, baby.
Okay, let's see here.
What's this?
Venomous curse?
Oh, right.
I have too many items.
Uh, let's put them in the... perks.
What perks do we have?
Peace with gods.
You make peace with your gods?
Huh?
Oh.
Uh, eat your vegetables.
You inflict more damage the more satiated you are, but you start losing health if your stomach... No, I don't want that.
Healthy exploration.
Every time you visit a new area, you regain 60 health?
I mean...
New area.
What...
What classified as a new area?
As in, I've entered the mines.
60 HP.
I've entered collapsed mines.
Or is it like... I don't know.
It's hard to say, right?
Let me not choose that yet, because I may have to re-roll.
What's this?
Death cross.
Oh.
Uh, yeah, let's put them in the water.
Just throw that in there.
I don't want this.
I also don't want that, honestly.
I don't want this either or that.
I don't want that.
Or that.
Oh, we're fine.
What's this?
Death cross.
Uh, what's this?
Liquid detonation.
Taking blast!
Ooh, I'm intrigued.
Square barrier.
No.
Accelerative homing.
Oh, man.
These are all very intriguing.
I may have to try death cross.
I need to see what that is.
A deadly energy cross that explodes after a short time.
Okay.
Let's try it.
Oh!
Oh.
Thank god I have explosion immunity, huh?
I for sure expected that to fly somewhere and explode.
Because it's not a static projectile.
Like that one other that just exploded in my face, if you remember.
Phew.
Okay.
Well, good to know.
I think I like this.
But oh, dude, this one?
Digging blast?
Sounds pretty dope as well.
Doesn't it?
Hmm.
Ah, man, it's tough.
I kind of want to spend my money on...
Nah, I don't know, man.
60 HP isn't even that much anymore now that I have 290 in total.
Let's reroll.
Projectile slower?
Oh.
That's not bad.
Summon Sedikivi.
You gain an artifact that allows you to call the Celestial Rage.
Okay.
Celestial Rage.
No more knockback.
This one could also be really nice, actually.
Yeah.
I think this one is the way to go.
I mean, this is just safety.
This one was incredible last time I tried it.
It's just good.
I'm taking it.
And then we spend the remaining money on new spells.
Uh, wait, Rock Spirit?
Liquid that... I mean...
Uh...
Let's think about this logically.
What would I like to replace, if anything?
I want my teleport to be a teleport.
Nothing else.
Oh, I have this, of course.
Causes, uh, maybe I don't need that in there.
Triples...
So hold on, this cast...
Wait, this is a sick wand, by the way.
Dude, this is actually...
This is actually an incredible wand.
Hold on a second.
Maybe I don't want this.
Uh...
Maybe I want to make this into an even more improved sniper.
Wait, what?
Oh, right.
Give me that.
Here.
Oh my god, stop.
Oh, fuck off.
Oh, that's so triggering right now.
What?!
Wait, what?
What just happened, dude?
No, what just happened?
What just happened?
Oh...
Wait.
Why was there electricity on that wand?
What?
I see the electricity on it.
Why was that on there?
I don't understand that.
Damn.
Fuck, I wanted to see what the next area was.
Oh well.
I guess I learned a lesson here, didn't I?
And the lesson is...
How about you don't put electricity in the water while you're in there, hmm?
That's... I think that's a good thing to learn here.
That is a valuable lesson we just learned.
And you know what else I learned this run?
How to make some sick... By the way, the first death doesn't count, remember?
Just saying.
We learned to make some crazy wands here.
We learned some combinations...
that are gonna be insane later on.
Okay.
Uh, I'm gonna go up here again, if I can.
Let's see.
I think I can actually, if I time this correctly.
Uh, wait, how do I time this correctly?
I would have to...
Oh wait, no, no, no.
Yikesy-dicey.
Okay, it's possible, but...
It is possible.
Nah, it's not possible.
Oh, what's up?
All right, well.
That happened.
Yep, let's just continue on.
I feel like that's a... we learned a valuable lesson now.
Nah, you know what?
I'm gonna start over that one.
That's, uh, that's not a good idea.
That's not a good idea.
I feel this is kind of cheating, because now I suddenly have this and I can go up here again.
Fuck it!
I'm doing it.
Here we go.
Let's get up here.
Bro, that run was incredible that I just had.
Wow!
I, like, I can't explain to you how much fun that was for me.
And I can't help but feel I'm just scratching the surface, you know?
But the... that whole... Oh, wow, that was so fun.
And I have one of my best... No, wait.
Nah, this is the shitty spell, never mind.
I thought it was my favorite.
Uh, up we go.
Besides, I couldn't even do this part with the normal bombs.
I don't know what I was thinking before.
What the fuck was I even doing?
I couldn't have, I couldn't have done this either.
This is so dumb.
Yoink!
No, come here.
Let's try and go up there again.
So when you put this tablet up there, you actually gain some money, believe it or not.
I figured that out last time.
Oh, wait, how do I get up there again?
How did I actually do this?
Oh, oh, yeah, right.
I have angered the demon below.
Ah, shit.
Uh...
Shit, if I had swamp water or mud, I could make a little mountain again like I did last time.
Shit, I don't think I can get up there.
It's uh...
Maybe I can if I really try for a long time, but I don't want to do that.
We got extra health, it's time to move on.
It's a good start.
In fact, you know what?
Next time, okay, the next time I get to the snowy depths, I am not gonna continue further down.
Because I know that connects to the mines.
Via the whole uh...
Uh...
The boss thingy like area.
You know what I mean.
So I'm gonna try that next time.
When I get there, I'm gonna try and get back up here and then I want to go up to the desert.
When I hopefully have some good ones.
Oh, but how do I get up that whole thing?
I would have to...
Oh, you know what?
Maybe that's not a big deal.
I can just jump along the side of a wall or something.
It should be okay.
All right, I'm tempted.
Hemis!
That's the first I've seen today.
What the hell?
Insane.
Oh, wow.
Hapsi.
I'm tempted to play impatient now, but I'm not gonna.
That's the mental strength that I have.
We're playing mega slow.
Hold on, I want to try and get in there.
Wait, how did that not... It's wood!
TNC doesn't destroy wood now?
Okay, here we go.
Release the water!
Why am I doing this?
Right to get up there.
Okay, well that didn't do much.
Go down here.
I think my favorite weapon right now is tied between, well, the two ones that I had.
It's got to be the electric arc or whatever.
Or, uh, hold on.
There we go.
Or the glowing lance.
I just absolutely love that.
It's so simple.
It's so good.
It's delicious, you know?
The way that it cuts through materials, fuck me, that's the best thing I've ever seen.
Hemis.
Hemis?
I'm obligated to say Hemis every time I see one.
It's in the contract.
Oh, shit.
Get... Let me through!
Come on!
Get out of there!
Let me!
Nice.
Yeah!
And I'm stuck.
Fuck you.
There we go.
Oh, no.
Made it.
I'm gonna come here and kill this guy.
I need your money.
80 gold already?
Not bad.
It's a good start.
How did I get through here last time?
Fuck off.
Huh?
Blow it up!
Fuck, this one sucks.
Took like six shots.
Oh, no.
I don't think I can fight that with what I have right now.
That's bad.
Hemis, though, I can deal with.
Acceleration.
Yes!
I love acceleration.
Accelerate me towards...
Lower it.
Wait.
What is burning there?
What is that down there?
Rotten meat.
The hell?
Why is that with an orange outline?
Oh, it's rusted.
I wonder if that's because it's in the water.
There's no way that's simulated.
Is that actually what's happening?
Because that's crazy.
No way.
No fucking way.
Honestly, it wouldn't surprise me at this point, you know?
This game is nuts.
Where am I going?
To the edge.
What is happening there?
Hold on.
Oh, that was the best shot I've ever made.
Okay, it's just so it was a bunch of coal around a bunch of oil.
Seems like a very bad thing to mix like that.
Yep.
We have a dude in here.
Uh-oh.
Maybe if he steps in this poison.
Damn.
Holy shit.
Sir.
Okay, he's burning.
He's burning.
So he does take fire damage.
Oh, wait a minute.
Water.
Watch.
Shit.
Let me take care of that guy first.
Come on now, dude.
Come on.
Come here.
This motherfucker.
Oh, he died.
Lovely stuff.
Lovely money.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Hemis.
I gotta get there.
I need to high-five them.
Oh, no.
That's like the way you greet Hemises.
You high-five.
And the best thing is they're gonna five you with all their five.
Oh, wait.
They only have three legs.
Uh...
Oops!
Someone shot me from behind.
Oh!
Whoa!
What?
Hello?
My dude has a wand!
Holy shit!
Burning hell.
Yo, that's insane!
Hand that over.
Can't play with that.
Only I can play with that.
Thank you.
Look at me.
I am the wizard.
Oh, I like this wand.
Much better.
That's now my number one.
What is this called?
Oh, this is just a spark bolt.
Hemis.
Yo, you can spam this.
There we go.
Holy shit!
What a congregation we have going on here.
Like, what is going on?
You know what?
That works.
Sometimes you gotta use some force.
Watch this.
What a neat circle that made, huh?
Circular explosion.
Come on, come on.
There we go.
Watch this.
Oil potion.
Sure.
Why not?
It's an oily hemis.
There they are.
Time to high five.
Oh, I'm slippery as hell.
Yo!
Yo, there we go.
What's up, dudes?
Yeah, I was coming through here.
What is...
What is this shiny stuff?
Oh.
The hell is that?
Shut...
What?
What just happened?
Hold on.
What the fuck just happened?
It hums slightly.
What happens if you kick it, you wonder?
Wait, is that what happened?
Motherfucker.
I hate this game.
I don't.
I love it.
But that was funny.
I think the first time you kick it, you get gold.
The second time it explodes.
I think that's what happens.
I think I accidentally kicked it while I was on the ground.
And that's why all the gold popped out.
That's my theory.
Sup, dudes?
Watch this.
Okay, that was not so good.
30 HP, it's getting a little bit risky here.
Wait, I have 600 gold right now.
Holy fuck!
I think we're ready to keep moving on then.
I kind of just want to find one more wand.
So I have at least one more.
You know, so I can put spells in it.
Seems like a pretty important thing.
What's going on here?
Nothing exploded.
Jesus.
Wow.
Things are popping off.
Let's not go that way.
I am deathly afraid of fire now.
It's like my most feared element in this game.
It feels like when I put water in the toxic sludge, that it requires way less water than you would think to turn it into all of it water.
You know what I mean?
Like, when I put blood into the toxic sludge, it felt like it's not the same effect.
Like, there's a difference.
Hold on.
Oh, come on.
Ah, it's burning.
Nice.
Let me in.
In fact, let me blow that up.
Shit, I'm an idiot.
What was this?
No, it was...
What is it?
Oh, it's phlamoxium.
Oh, look at the phlamoxium.
It contains all the colors.
I wonder if that's because it's a mix of all the different chemicals in the game.
And that's why you get confused when you drink it.
You're like, what the fuck am I ingesting?
Ah, we've got to do it up there.
Fall in the water, yeah!
You noob.
I'm actually so glad that I figured that out.
Can I make a water gun?
You know, I just want to be able to spray water on them.
Like, a Super Soaker.
That's like, that's their kryptonite.
Just have a Super Soaker 3000.
Like, in one of those kids' commercials from the 90s.
I kind of just want to find an HP upgrade somewhere here.
Before I go through the portal.
You know what I mean?
Just a little taste.
Just want a little taste.
30 HP, I mean.
Oh, I want nice.
Very nice.
Collapsed?
You feel wary?
What?
Why do I feel wary?
I don't like feeling wary.
What's happening?
No, I don't like that.
Holy shit.
There was a bunch of chemicals up there!
Alright, we're going to wait a bit.
And we're going to pour water.
The thing about water in this game, it doesn't seem to put out flames that well.
Like, it's a bit hit and miss, you know?
Like, you would think these flames go out, but they don't.
Okay, they sort of do, but yeah.
Was this burst of air?
Sure.
I will take that with me on my travels.
Bye-bye.
I'm glad that I haven't been accustomed to...
being explosion immune.
I'm still very much scared of being exploded, so...
That's good.
Sir, I see you.
Did he go all the way down here?
Wow.
Okay,
I think it's time.
No, actually, hold on.
I want to check out the wary thing.
I felt wary or something over here.
What does that mean?
Ooh, that's a mine.
That's a mine.
Let's be careful there.
We've got creepy ambience sounds.
It's only down here.
Frogs.
There's another wand over there, too.
Uh...
This thing is spraying blood like crazy.
Blow up everything.
Trigger that.
Okay, good.
Let's go this way.
I still have bombs to get in there, worst case.
Oh man, oh man, oh man.
Purifying powder.
That's pretty good.
That's a good thing.
Oh!
Yo, the frog did 10 damage!
These things don't fuck around.
Okay, frogs are bad.
I thought they were a bit of a meme, but I guess not.
What are these background sounds?
There we go.
Let's see what we got.
Ooh.
Circle of shielding.
Uh, I think I had this one before.
I think I had that one before at some point.
Um...
Bouncing.
Oh, you know what?
0.15, 0.45.
Maybe I want that instead of this.
Then again.
This one has 55...
I can't judge what is better.
It's so difficult for me.
I don't know.
Uh...
Shit.
What?
0.05... Okay, 0.05, 0.43.
The lower these numbers, the better, honestly.
Like, in general, it's just better.
But the mana charge speed is just a little lower there.
So maybe I want to keep this.
So that means...
Let's replace this one.
Yeah.
That seems like the right choice.
Okay.
That's for you, sir.
It died from that!
You saw that?
Just having that fall on his head killed him.
What the... Oh no.
I should go back, shouldn't I?
Fuck.
Okay.
You know what?
I'm gonna go back.
Yeah, we're finding the portal now.
20 HP is, uh, scary.
There's a bunch of... Wait, here it is.
Yeah, there it is.
Uh-oh, we've got a thing lying in wait.
I think I'm just gonna jump in the portal.
There we go.
Beautiful.
I wonder if they can follow me into the portal.
Oh, okay.
135 HP now.
Yo, this one looks sick.
I don't know about that one.
This one seems like it could very quickly kill you.
And then we have... What is that?
I'm intrigued.
Uh, I know that one.
Oh, these!
Ooh, I think I know what to buy.
I'm gonna buy this one.
It's also half off.
Replace it with that one.
And then I want to buy this one.
Nope, not that one.
This one.
Replace it with...
Oh, that's one.
I can always put it back, I guess.
Eldritch portal.
Summons a one-way portal to a sinister realm.
What?
Uh, I am very intrigued by that.
But let me wait with that.
Okay.
Hold on a minute.
That seems a little cray cray.
Hold on, this is a 0.18.
This is one spell.
So honestly, none of this matters.
This is...
Well, this is three spells, so this can go here.
Let's see this one.
Wait, why is that not shooting?
Oh, probably because I don't have enough mana, right?
160 mana.
Oh, dude.
Ho ho ho ho.
Not bad.
Hello?
We can even... Wait!
Holy sh... Dude, watch this!
If this works the way I think it does...
Watch this.
Uh, no, no, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We're gonna do this instead.
Uh...
We're gonna do...
Wait a minute.
This one here.
Two.
This is one.
This right here.
This casts two spells.
What are those spells?
It's these two.
One, two.
Because this acts as one batch.
This acts as another batch.
Watch.
Oh, but do we have enough mana?
We'll have to find out, but let's see.
Wait.
Uh, hold on.
Oh, wait.
Oh, it's not shuffle.
Okay.
So, what's happening?
It's doing... Oh, wait, this is three.
Oh, okay.
Wait, this means it wraps around and does this again.
Oh, the mana is slow as hell.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, that's horrible!
Damn.
So, this is a one-shot thing, huh?
When you use this... Oh, that's terrible, actually.
Holy shit.
Wow.
Okay, never mind.
Never mind.
I think my idea works in practice.
It's just very impractical now, because...
that mana recharge is atrocious.
So, uh, let me test my thing.
You know what?
Let's see what else we got.
Um...
Hmm.
I may be... Hold on.
0.25, 0.25.
250 mana.
How much mana do I need for this?
80.
Oh, it's ice meter towards... Uh, hmm.
Yeah.
I need 320 at least.
Hold on.
Do I even have that on this?
I do... Oh, 480.
Yeah, okay.
So, it's a big trade-off here.
I mean, it's possible to do a crazy spell with that.
Maybe I do just want to do it.
You know?
I mean, it's not gonna be great.
But whatever.
In fact, I can just do this, because...
two spells.
This is...
one spell.
And...
this is the other.
Maybe it won't use as much per...
I mean...
It's not bad.
But it's kind of bad, you know?
So, this actually makes it go really fast.
The only issue is that mana recharge is so slow.
This could potentially be a quick want, because we are technically circumventing the recharge time on this.
Because, look.
This casts two spells.
This is one of those spells.
Uh, and that spell is a double, right?
So, uh...
That means this one is being cast, but this one is three.
So, one, two, and the next one is a whole new spell, which is the whole sequence again.
So, this has potential to do something crazy, if it wasn't for the shitty mana recharge shit, you know?
I'm gonna leave a list like this, I think.
This is cool.
Whoops, don't throw that in there.
Grab it.
What was on this thing?
Right, I also have this.
Wait a minute.
What's going on here?
What is that?
A circle of shit?
Right, let me see.
Okay, yeah.
Uh, I'm not too intrigued by that, honestly.
I do like this.
This is a solid...
damage want, you know?
In fact, why not just do this?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, I have an idea, I have an idea, I have an idea.
Uh...
Oh, it's shuffle.
Ooh, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad.
I hate that.
Uh, wait, 0.03.
Ah, crap cake.
Do I have other wands here that are crazy like that?
Let's see here, 0.25.
0.05?
Buy it.
Let's try it with this one.
I have so much money anyway, who cares?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no, this is not doing what I expected to then.
Because I expected this one to...
cast three spells.
This one, that one, and what's the next?
That one again.
Which, oh...
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Unless I do this.
Two spells.
One.
Two.
Dip, dip.
Let me just try.
It's so weird how these things interact like that.
It's very interesting.
Sometimes you don't know what's gonna happen, so just try and play around with it a bit.
Okay.
Not superly exciting, I gotta say.
What was that sound over here?
There was a sound that just stopped.
Weird.
Since the realm.
What if I just do this?
How much mana does it have?
190, so it's... I can do two.
I mean, mana recharge is actually not bad on that.
Uh, 45.
Can I... Can I make a sick one like that?
Hold on.
Mana charge 200.
Hello.
Now hold on a second.
No.
Put some stuff up here.
Like that.
Buy this one, replace it with... I think that one.
And now we can do...
Also, I have a bunch of dynamite now.
I mean, put that here for now.
Be careful not to start this one, huh?
We're gonna go... No shuffle on this, by the way.
Mana charge speed is insane.
So...
Oh, what is max mana?
Oh, max mana sucks.
Oh, no.
I didn't look at that.
I'm an idiot.
Oh, no, it doesn't work.
Ah, shit.
I don't have what I need.
That's unfortunate.
But maybe I can do something else with this.
Something crazy.
We can do... it casts three spells, right?
So, I mean...
Why not just do something like this?
Put all this stuff in here.
Put this one there.
So that's one, two.
That's bop, bop.
Like, oh wait, how much mana does it cost?
I think we have enough for this.
Let me just try this.
All the recharge.
So wait, we can... we can circumvent.
We can circumvent by doing...
by doing this, I think.
No, wait.
How... how that work?
One, two...
Maybe it doesn't work with the double spell.
So this casts two spells, right?
Oh, I understand why.
That's why.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Choose this spell and that spell.
And this spell consists of this spell and that spell.
So why does this not...
Oh, wait, because it casts three spells at once.
That's why.
That is why.
That is actually why.
Um, how can I circumvent?
One, two...
So one is...
So this is one.
Two.
Uh...
Like that?
Not quite.
I'm trying to circumvent the whole recharge thing.
But it's difficult when there's three spells.
Oh, because yeah, it's not gonna work.
I'm gonna need a lot to make this work, then.
Shit.
Okay.
How about we try this one, then?
Spells cast is one.
So this one should be...
Okay.
So if I do that now...
Let me see here.
It always just shoots this one, which is these two pl... Why doesn't that loop around them?
Why doesn't that loop around?
Uh...
That's actually something I don't understand.
Why... This should loop around.
This shoots three spells.
One, two...
Three.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm an idiot.
This counts as one spell.
No, no, this should work.
That's so weird.
Okay, I don't know.
Let me just experiment.
Okay, that's faster.
All right.
It's weird the different effects you get, right?
When you just mess around with things.
Also, what perks do I have?
Homonculus.
Every time you leave a holy mountain, a helpful homonculus is summoned.
Okay.
Levitation trail.
When levitating, you leave a trail of magical sparks that harm passing creatures.
Trick blood money.
Blood money is dropped when death is an accident.
So when I die, I get money for the next run.
Because that seems pretty shit.
I don't want to focus on the next run.
I want to focus on this run.
I have no idea what that just means.
What?
That makes no sense.
Oh, I can't even... Oh, I shouldn't have spent all that money.
Uh, well, I guess... You know what?
I want my homonculus.
Every time you leave, a helpful homonculus is summoned.
Fantastic.
I can't wait to see the homonculus.
All right, let's not fuck around too much.
I just want to make a simple wand that shoots things and kills things.
So how about we do...
Uh, mana.
Wrong wand.
Give me...
Honestly, give me that one, I think.
Or...
170, 250.
This one.
Give me that instead.
I'm just gonna make this one that I had in mind before.
I think.
Eh, I forgot how I did it.
Let's percast one, so... one.
Oh, wait.
One, two.
Boom, there it is.
Oh, yeah.
But it actually uses up all my mana.
This is actually insane.
Maybe I don't want it then.
All right, this is fine.
Let's just leave this at how it is.
The next one...
My standard damaging wand.
I think I just want it to be...
I mean, that's not bad, you know.
That's a solid wand right there.
Oh, homunculus is here.
Look at the homunculus.
Where am I?
There.
0.05.
If I can make this do a little more funny things here, I would be very happy.
Not
bad.
Hello?
That's awesome.
Wait.
Dude, look at this!
Holy fucking shit!
That...
Oh, you know what?
Did I reach a castile of zero with this?
Is that what's happening?
Oh, no, wait.
It's still super slow still, though.
Oh, wait, I think I am circumventing.
I'm circumventing the recharge.
By doing this.
That's what's happening.
What an insane wand.
What?
I mean, okay.
And that just works.
If I can somehow focus this heavy spread, imagine.
Wouldn't that be crazy?
What the hell, man?
I want to be able to focus the powers that be.
I mean, it's not super useful.
It shoots fast, but it's just everywhere, right?
That's the trade-off you make.
God damn it, man.
I don't know.
I'm so indecisive with this.
I'm so indecisive.
How did I make this one the way I had before?
Maybe it was just like that.
I don't remember.
Oh, I was about to say, when you switch wands, the mana stays.
And it's being remembered for that wand.
That never occurred to me until now.
For some reason, I thought it was just a universal mana bar that...
Yeah, I don't know how that would work, I guess, but that makes sense.
So when I switch to this wand, you know, I have a separate mana bar.
When I switch back, it's still recharging.
That's cool.
Yeah, so I can actually just switch to it, expel all the mana, boom, next wand, you know, just use my standard.
That's not a bad idea.
I still think I want this.
It's a solid weapon.
I mean, you know, it's not great.
It's fine.
This one, though.
Also pretty cool.
In fact, no, actually.
Yeah, hey!
I mean, yeah.
Pretty cool.
I think I'll run with that, and then I'll try this and that one.
And that's fine.
We just leave this like this.
Although dynamite?
Dynamite.
Uh...
So I'm gonna do this instead.
I'm gonna use this as dynamite.
There we go.
And then this is gonna be my damaging wand.
And something a little different.
Let's move on.
Let's fucking move on.
I spent way too much time in here, man, but it's too much fun building these wands.
Let's move.
The cold pits.
Okay, if you're humongous, are you gonna kill him?
Hey, dude!
Whoa.
My dude is actually useful.
I wonder if he can die.
But the enemy's gonna focus him.
That's the question.
Hey, you like slime?
The slime doesn't like slime.
Isn't that weird?
Wow, 14 because it shoots two at a time.
Not bad at all.
I missed that.
I wanted to kick it.
The good thing about this slime, I can actually cut through environments with it.
It is corrosive.
I hear burning.
We have a fireman.
Energy orb with a timer.
Say what?
We gotta try that.
So wait, after a certain time, what happens?
It's... Wow!
Oh, cool!
I mean, it's slow as heck, right?
But uh...
It does a lot of damage when you hit him.
Not bad.
That's pretty cool.
Okay, but I want the other one.
In fact, I'm gonna try this now.
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, shit!
Oh, I thought I could go inside of them!
I was bamboozled!
Hold on, let me try that again.
Why does it say it to a sinister realm?
Oh my god.
Man, the projectiles on this are too slow.
I mean, they barely work.
Hold on.
Let me go up here.
Let me try that once more.
Let me try and do it and run away.
Shoot it!
Eldritch portal.
I mean, I guess I can use it to put it somewhere and then have it attack a bunch of enemies, right?
In fact, I'm gonna do that with the next enemy I see.
Whoa, it's a rat.
Maybe not with that.
Whoa, don't hit my homonculus!
Sir, for that you get an eldritch portal.
Hey, fun!
Oh, that actually insta- Homonculus!
Oh, I thought he died to the eldritch portal.
Okay.
All right.
You know what?
That can be useful against the boss.
Wow, I took damage!
That was no joke.
That's for you.
Oh, yeah, it's actually effective as hell.
That thing is killer.
Summon those eldritch horrors.
Let me get the gold.
I kind of want to go to the boss now and try this eldritch portal on it.
Oh, I only have one left.
Wait a minute.
Did I?
Wait.
Do I only have one left or do I have 11 left?
Hold on.
Whoa!
Okay, I have more.
I have more.
Perfect.
All right.
Pretty cool.
I do feel like we're kind of low on hp though for that sort of thing.
Also, I get the feeling this eldritch portal is supposed to be coming after a trigger.
Because the summoning it right in front of me is a little bit questionable.
Hell yeah.
The fact that I can do this is actually big.
I have to consider this toxic slush spell an actual digging thing.
Ah, it doesn't work on everything, but on some things.
Come on homunculus.
We have adventure.
Give me some upgrades before I enter the portal.
All right, fine.
Keep going.
I feel like we're so early in the run.
I need more money though.
Nice.
It's a solid spell.
It does a lot of damage.
Of course, it's slow, but...
Okay, so watch this.
Uh...
Look at how little water I need.
Look how it's spreading!
Amazing.
What do we have here?
Bouncing burst?
Add mana?
Triple scatter?
Ooh.
Hmm.
I mean...
Not bad.
Hello.
Oh, it's a little bit... very inaccurate actually.
I don't think I want it, but I do want it because of the add mana.
And a bunch of these could be nice to have.
So instead I'm gonna change it up and replace...
I don't know what to replace.
Maybe this one.
I already have another one of those at home.
Yeah, let's bring that with us.
Seems like a worthwhile thing to do.
Uh, my god, homunculus is affected by all kinds of elements.
Come here!
You're taking damage.
Don't stand in the toxic sludge.
Okay.
I do wonder if I can hide somewhere in the boss fight and homunculus will just kill the boss.
Uh, do I go through yet?
Fuck.
I think I do.
25 hp.
You know, it's just not very much.
It's not the greatest run so far.
But things can change.
A boulder.
Always casts mana.
Whoa!
That's a lot.
That's a lot of those.
And what is that?
That's a fire bolt?
I think?
With trigger?
0.03, 0.57.
Let's see here.
Let me just look at the stats.
17, 0.20, 0.12.
I like it.
I like this.
No, it's 0.20.
That's actually kind of slow, isn't it?
Spells cast is two.
I think I like this one.
I think I like it 0.20.
Is this the slowest?
You know what?
I like it because of all the spells that it contains.
But then again, I just thought about this.
If I do this, I can have a shit ton of bombs always at the ready.
You know?
But maybe I don't want that all the time.
Minus 2.0 degrees, 200.
Oh wait, this is a shuffle.
Fuck.
That's bad.
I am gonna get this one.
Give me this.
Uhhh...
Do that.
Okay, man, I have a shit ton of dynamite and bombs.
Bombs though?
Destroys ground very efficiently.
This is just a small explosive.
I don't like this.
The Eldritch Portal.
I gotta be honest.
That's a little bit, you know?
Not really my thing.
So hold on.
I had an issue before with lacking mana recharge, right?
But if I can...
Effectively add 30 mana every time I shoot.
That could change things.
So the little experiment I had before...
How much mana is this?
310.
That's not bad.
We could make some stuff happen.
Uh, unless I...
Wait a minute.
I need to put this somewhere here first.
Put these in the water.
And then take it back.
No, that's the wrong bond, isn't it?
Wait, I'm so confused.
Wait a minute.
No, no, no.
I am... I have no idea what I'm doing.
I am so confused.
I wanted to do this one again.
Oh, but I'm missing one of these double spells now, because I... I left them in the thing, didn't I?
But we have this.
So one, two, like that.
That's one, two...
Three.
So if I now...
Add this in the front.
The recharge is nice.
What am I limited by?
That's just doing...
Oh wait, this needs to be first, I think.
Double...
Double spell, right?
Modifier, multicast.
So, this one is going to cast three spells.
Which is one, two, three.
And this spell is two spells.
Oh, this is getting confusing.
Where the first spell is that one.
Oh, that's fucked up.
What?
Yeah, that messes with my brain.
I just want to be able to make this shoot a little faster.
This is just a little atrocious right now.
Right, that's bad.
I mean...
I don't know, man.
Actually, not bad.
Let me see this first one.
Actually, sick.
Cast two spells per cast, so that's one.
And...
That's two.
Wait, why is that so slow?
All the recharge time, shit.
So, maybe if I do add this...
One.
Two.
One, two, three.
Shit, how did I do this just the other day?
Or just today, actually.
I don't remember exactly when, but...
I made this go super fast somehow.
I'm just gonna experiment a little bit.
So, one, two, three, which is two.
So, if I go like that...
Man, it's not an issue here at all.
It's the recharge time that is limiting me.
Of 0.85 seconds, right?
And...
I just wanted to wrap around, I guess, like I did with that other one.
But I forgot how I did it.
So, one, two, three.
Where this three... Oh, we need an extra then, right?
Or maybe not.
Where this three is two spells.
One.
No, it is like that, because look.
This one shoots three spells.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Spells per cast is two!
Hold your horses.
I'm being foiled again by this.
I'm bambooshed so hard.
So, it's actually not doing what I think.
It's doing that first.
One spell?
Okay, so, we have to think.
Oh, god.
So, every batch within a batch is what I have to think about.
Triple scatter.
Let's start with a triple for now.
Let's start with a double, just to understand.
It shoots two as one.
So, that means the very first thing that's being spelled here is expelled is this.
This is one spell right now.
Right?
And that one spell contains a double.
Oh, that's...
That is so fucked up.
Hold on.
No, no, I'm misunderstanding.
Spells per cast is two, so that means...
The first spell being cast is that one, of course, which is a double spell.
Which means the very first spell being cast is actually these three.
The next spell being cast on the same click...
is now that one, which contains three.
One, two, and the next one goes around.
Fuck me, it's not doing... Let me look at the board.
So, it's... Oh, it's doing mana as well, actually.
It's doing mana to here.
That's not what I wanted to do.
I wanted to do something funky here.
See, I do this.
Okay.
So, I click once, and all of this executes.
Which makes sense, because that's what's supposed to happen, right?
Two spells are being cast when I click the button.
The first spell is this, which goes all the way to here.
The second spell is this, which wraps all around these three.
So, this is two spells being cast with one click.
Makes total sense.
Now, how can I use this to make some damage happen?
If I now do that, then this triple scatter spell, which is the second spell of the click, will now also fire another multicast.
Oh, but that's gonna be messy.
That's...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What if I start mixing it like this instead?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Three spells.
This is the first.
No, two spells.
One, two, three.
That's Uno.
The next one is that.
My god, I don't know... Fuck!
I don't know how I did this.
I did...
do some... Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe I'm... Maybe my whole assumption of when I sort of broke the game, or the exploit thingy that I discovered, maybe that... Maybe that was sort of an exploit for that specific spell or something.
Maybe this is not a universal rule, what I'm thinking here.
I need to stop doing this.
I'm losing my mind.
I'm absolutely losing my mind here.
We need to just stop.
Let's just do this.
So that shoots these two only right now.
So if I add this here, that's one spell, which is these two, and then the next one is that one.
So that shoots a bunch.
That's a bunch of damage right there in one shot.
It's not bad.
It's really nice, actually.
And they do three damage per... Maybe it's better with... Oh, wait a minute.
These remove cast delay.
These ones... Why do... Oh, crit chance is up.
Oh, okay.
All right.
What if I do this?
One, two, one.
Shit, man.
This game is complicated when it comes to the spells.
This is something else, isn't it?
This adds a lot of degrees.
So that would be one, two, three.
That's one.
And the other one is...
That's a lot.
That's not bad at all.
One, two...
But this one is a little less spready, isn't it?
It's still sort of spready, I guess.
It's almost gonna spread these three no matter what.
That's unfortunate.
So maybe it's just better to do without all of these.
It's a bit boring.
Maybe this is just better.
Oh my god, it is just better.
Fuck this stupid wand.
It sucks.
I hate it.
I'm going back to basics.
Whoops.
Oh, what?
No.
I didn't mean to throw that away.
This is now my damaging wand.
It's just a single bouncing burst.
Fuck.
It's too good.
What can you say?
I mean, fuck.
Let's throw away a bunch of this.
We don't need it.
And a bunch of these.
Okay, so my second wand, let's just get to this.
It's gonna be a bunch of bombs, isn't it?
Let's not have one that shoots two at a time.
Let's do this one instead.
This is my bomb one.
So, bomb, bomb.
Uh, give me two more bombs.
There we go.
Uh, bomb here.
And wait, where's the other bomb?
There.
That's my bomb one.
Shoots bombs.
It's great.
The next one is gonna be this.
This can't kill me, hopefully.
Let me just test.
Can this kill me?
I'm not sure.
There's also a bit of a delay when you shoot it.
It's not instantaneous, which is a bit alarming.
Don't like that.
In fact, I hate all my wands.
This is terrible.
I hate all of this right now.
It's horrible.
I'm just gonna fill shit up with dynamite.
Dynamites and bombs.
I don't care.
Let's get some use out of it.
Let's just explode everything we see.
Seems like a good time.
There we go.
Bunch of bombs.
Shoots a bunch at the same time.
It's a mess.
We love it.
I'm gonna grab the other two things down here.
There we go.
And put those here.
There.
Here.
Why not?
In fact, put these two here.
One, two, three.
One, two.
There we go.
Fuck yeah.
That seems like a good selection here.
We move on.
Recharge my shit.
I'm not happy with these wands at all.
I'm really not.
But it's okay.
Oh, I didn't even check the perks.
What the fuck?
Stainless armor.
You take 50% less damage as long as you have active stain status effect.
Oh.
Isn't that really, like, big?
Cordyceps?
Oh, fungal creature spawn.
Faster movement.
Your movement's... Oh.
I mean, that's a no-brainer, I think.
But then again, I'm always sort of stained in some way or fashion.
I think this is really big.
I'm taking the stain armor.
Incredible.
All right, dude.
Let's fucking go.
There's a wand right here.
Okay.
Imagine it was just gonna replace one of my wands again.
Let's see what this does.
Oh.
Wait, what?
Oh, homunculus, you saved my life.
Dude.
That is an insane wand.
How come this didn't work like that when I tried it last time?
I tried these digging bolts.
They did nothing when I tried.
Holy shit!
Wow.
Okay, well, I'm replacing the...
It's done.
I'm using this as my number one.
And we're going with the digging one instead of the bombs.
What the hell?
That's insane.
Whoops.
Homunculus!
Oh, shit.
Uh, yeah, my wand sucks.
We definitely need to find a better wand.
But we are in the snowy depths.
That's why we found that insane wand last time.
Maybe we have similar luck this time.
Because this... I mean, it may be fast, but it's such low damage.
It's incredibly hilariously bad.
If you think about it, the wand I had last time here did 300 something damage when I hit them.
This does three damage a pop.
Oh my god, stop sniping me.
Did he die?
Homunculus, you saved me.
You're an incredible... I have two humunculi!
Kill him.
Dude, I'm being carried by my humunculi.
And I love it.
They're saving my ass.
Oh, what's up?
Shit's going down down there.
Wait, I'm taking damage?
Oh, I see.
I see.
Holy shit.
Get him, humunculi.
Nice.
Dude, they're so sick.
I'm burning.
Lotus.
Okay, the digging bolt.
One of my favorite spells now.
I love it.
Come here, sir.
You want to dance?
I feel like I'm killing my enemies, but it's actually not me.
It's my humunculi.
Insane wand.
And it's infinite.
I can infinitely do this.
How is that not broken AF?
Wait, how... This looks like a place I've already been.
But I guess it's not.
Weird.
Wait, why do things go dark again?
That's odd.
Usually it doesn't.
It usually lights up forever after you've been there.
The hell?
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
I can't fight this.
We got to leave.
Humunculi.
Save me.
I just got to go down.
Wait, wait, wait.
I wanted to try and go up, didn't I?
So now we can dig.
So last time I went to the boss area, I went down through where the hanging bridge was.
And then I encountered a sniper to the left of me.
So I have to go up and right, I believe.
I have to dig up and right.
Just dig.
Let's just dig somewhere.
Yo, what the hell is this?
They have a little home here.
Uh-oh.
Kill them, Humunculi.
Oh, they're snipers.
This is a bad spot to be in.
I can just do this.
Wow.
That is actually wild.
Oh, I came to the wrong neighborhood.
Holy shit.
Look at all the blood falling.
Oh, it's a big guy.
Wait, I think one of my Humunculi died.
Unfortunate as it is.
They are killing it.
Look.
Hell yeah.
Sick.
Actually, the best companions ever.
Oh, fuck.
I thought I could pick it up.
Damn.
Okay.
Shit.
I learned my lesson.
Did he die?
He did.
Oh my god, I'm almost dead.
Whoa.
Okay, I can't dig through this.
Holy shit, I can.
Yo, I can dig through this as well.
Dude.
What?
I gotta find the edge of the level and try and dig.
I have to.
Whoa, what is this place?
Bunch of rats.
This is gonna be an exploratory investigative mission.
Not so much trying to progress too much because my wand sucks.
I'm gonna... It's gonna really be just trying crazy things.
Until I find a great wand.
In that case, I'll maybe change my... Wait a minute.
This is it.
If I go up here.
Right?
Yeah, look, I remember this.
I fell from here.
I can totally get up again.
Easy peasy.
Watch.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I'm excited.
It's a long way up.
Is this even allowed going back like this?
This is crazy.
Well, this is gonna be some kind of crazy changed version of this place.
I can technically make a little place to stand in there with this digging thing.
Like look.
Oh, maybe not.
Oh,
I'm down.
Can I actually... Okay, I cannot actually dig through this.
I thought I could.
Oh man, how am I gonna...
Acceleration.
But it's not gonna get me higher.
It's only gonna get me more horizontally.
Drink.
Oh yeah, that's... Yeah!
Oh wait,
I can't...
Oh, I broke that shit.
So hold on.
There's gonna be a... You know what?
Before I do that, let's go back here.
I just want to see.
Am I actually just gonna be back?
Did Homonculus just fall in the fucking lava and die?
Is that what just happened?
Yeah, Tabula's Mardina is the same.
Seems like we are back.
Oh, we are definitely back.
Homonculus is summoned?
Wait, because I entered this place?
Awesome.
I'm gonna go to the surface now.
Look!
It's the ro... Oh yeah, it's the exact same place.
It's the rusted thingy.
I left you out, didn't I?
Did they drop money still?
I want to go back up to the surface.
Wait, what am I doing?
I just dig!
I'm a digging monster!
Oh, it's tough, but it's doable.
Oh yeah, dude.
We made it to the surface!
Wait, stainless?
Oh!
I misread this.
I thought this meant as long as I have a stain, I'll take less damage.
I mean, not that I actively tried to get a stain.
I actually sort of forgot about it, but I totally...
How was that laser just now?
Wait, was that a bounce from... It probably was.
So this thing is gonna... Wait, is it not taking any damage because the projectile has been slow?
This guy's dying from... No!
Homunculus!
Come on, follow me.
Don't drown.
That would be terrible.
We are going on an adventure, you and I.
Yeah,
where the fuck am I?
This has become a whole different game here.
Yo, this is crazy.
Okay, that's... I think that's the bottom.
Extremely dense, yeah.
All right.
Pretty cool though.
I feel invisible with this digging spell.
I want to go to the... Can I dig in those temples, I wonder?
In fact, I have a tablet on me.
Maybe I can do... Oh!
I forgot about this wand doing that.
I'm sorry!
Sorry, forest fire.
It's all right.
Yo, enemies!
What?
Am I crazy or is this faster than normal?
It's normally not that fast.
Brother.
Unreal.
Wait, there's... Hold on, let me excavate.
I thought I just did something crazy, but I didn't.
Never mind.
It's desert time, baby.
414 gold.
I thought just something just happened again, because the music happened to come in right when I did that.
Unfortunately, I can't dig in that brickwork, it seems.
That's sad.
I want to excavate these things.
Hello.
What's happening here?
Okay, Humunkelai, are you ready?
Get him!
Uh oh.
Yo, where... Oh!
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
Humunkelai, protect me.
Just do it.
Six seconds of this nonsense here.
Dude, this is a bad situation we're in.
Look at this weird rock formation here.
Uh oh.
Oh, that's real bad.
That's just terrible.
Oh, there's a guy.
Oh, wow.
Get him, Humunkelai.
Shit, I'm sorry.
He died.
Couldn't handle my TNT.
Yo, what is this place, yo?
Oh, what?
Okay, I'm scared.
This game is nuts.
Where am I?
Holy shit!
That's for you.
Dude, the Humunkelai are actually helping so much.
Help me, help me.
Kill him.
Get him.
Oh, fuck.
Yo!
Low on mana, low on mana.
Low on HP, low on everything.
Got him.
This place is nuts.
I don't know what's going on.
Where are we?
Look at the markings in the back.
We're definitely in some kind of temple area.
And I'm just going deeper and deeper here.
Shit!
Wow.
Damn.
Okay.
I am scared, man.
I am scared of the unknown.
I have no idea what's going on in this area.
This is all very mysterious to me.
I love that, though.
I love that.
That's so good.
But it's been a long time.
I gotta stop now.
Gotta stop now.
That was a crazy session.
What a run.
All right, I'm opening chat.
Let me actually put this on.
I'm gonna put some music for me.
You can't hear it, but I just need something.
Hemis.
Verilite was a great gaming sesh.
It was.
I got so far.
I actually...
It was almost a no-death stream.
I should have quit while I was ahead.
That would have been a no-death stream, then.
What's my favorite spell?
Oh, that's a good one.
I think my favorite spell is...
I think it's the Glowing Lance.
I think it's called.
The one I used to snipe enemies with.
The one that cuts through and everything like butter.
Fucking love that one.
I also love the electricity arc or the electricity bomb that goes...
That's a great one.
In fact, that whole run convinced me those two spells were my favorite.
So far, I don't know what's out there.
Glowing Lance, that's it.
Yeah, that one.
Love the Glowing Lance.
I love that it penetrates enemies and keeps going.
Shuffle's a good spell.
Yep.
Hey Oliver, do you want to know why wants weren't working as you wish or you prefer to find out by yourself?
Definitely the latter.
I'm gonna figure it out in time.
I just need to experiment more, but the thing is it's fun.
It's really fun experimenting.
That's why I do it so much.
I don't mind.
It's fun to figure it out.
How was your favorite moment to stream?
Also Chad has decided I was your homunculus wife.
Maybe I'll call the little homunculus news of PE from now on.
It's just the way of science indeed.
How did you feel after the first death?
I feel great.
I mean the death was a little anticlimactic, of course.
But it was a lesson learned, you know.
Don't go into the water with the electricity.
But that run was so much fun.
It was, you don't even understand how much fun I had with that.
Very few games give me this amount of...
What do you even call it?
Just sustained fun that never goes down, you know?
Like all the time.
It's very very cool.
You always die in noiter eventually.
That's true.
Immunity saved you so many times.
Yeah, of course, but I also played like that because I knew I had immunities, right?
I probably wouldn't have been blowing shit up left and right if I didn't.
So...
The experimentation and exploration is so fun in this game.
It is.
And you know what I get about this game?
I get this feeling that there are these great mysteries to be found.
Like the thing I just discovered there at the end, you know?
Just going deeper?
I didn't even know what to expect.
I just tried that for the heck of it.
I went down...
...and all kinds of weird shit took place.
You know, there was... it was a weird underground temple and there were so many enemies.
Like, what the hell is going on?
I love not knowing what's going on.
It's great.
Hey, military pawn and a laevie.
What's up, a laevie?
It's been a while.
How you doing?
Thank you for that.
Thank you for subscribing with the Prime and gifting a community sub.
You guys are awesome.
170 subscribers.
That's just unreal.
Someone raided near the beginning?
Really?
Oh no, how do I see this?
Filtered by...
Kravak.
That's awesome.
I don't know who you are, Kravak, but thank you so much.
If you're there right now.
Probably not, but if you are, I appreciate that a lot.
Thank you.
Is anyone still here from that raid?
I wonder.
I think most people just sort of bounce immediately after a raid, right?
Like, when I raid someone after this, I think most people say hi and then they're just bounced, which is fine.
I do the same.
As a... as a viewer.
I'm gonna play your first run seat this weekend.
It was really nice.
Wait, how do you do that?
How do you know my run seat?
Is that something you can see?
It's... I'm fine.
I wasn't watching your videos for quite some time, as you played games that I either planned to play myself or didn't care about.
Yeah, that's fair.
So you have played Noita, I imagine.
But you know what that means?
That means you have a lot of great games to look forward to playing, because I've only played bangers lately.
Almost.
Almost only.
From the pause screen.
Ah, okay, cool.
I didn't even realize you could have a seat like that.
I mean, I realized it was random, but that you could actually write it down and do the same seat.
Of course, that would make sense, given that there is this daily challenge where everyone plays the same seat.
I seed hunt?
And if you press escape, you can see the seed.
Mods let you pick seats.
Oh, okay.
There's a mod that can change the seat.
Oh, yeah, right.
That's what this just said.
Yeah, it's gonna be in the Heezy Base, for sure.
P .E.
The worlds are 100% deterministic.
What do you mean by that?
I mean, I know what the words you say mean, but in the context of this game, what does that mean?
Unless it's a spoiler of some sort.
I feel like Heezy Base honeymoon would be very explosive.
Would be a lot of fun, though.
It's so demon.
Yeah.
Feels so weird.
I'm listening to music.
You guys can't hear it.
It's so... Oh, actually, wait a minute.
I can actually do this.
Because on Twitch, you can actually have an audio track that is being broadcasted and then an audio track that will only be there in the VOD.
So I could technically put on music right now and it would not be in the VOD.
No, I'm listening to...
Can I kick it from a tribe called Quest?
I don't know how many of you are into rap.
Just go on Spotify.
Can I kick it?
It's a classic.
It is a classic, yes.
People do that to avoid copyright strikes.
Yeah, it sounds awesome.
You know what?
Dude, I should just do that from now on.
That solves all my issues with that.
I think you can get strikes from music on Twitch, but they just mute the section of the VOD.
Yes, that's entirely correct, Frank.
But I can make it so that the music I play on stream will not show up in the VOD.
That's a whole different audio track.
So I just make sure to play anything that is copyrighted while I'm live and that will never show up on the stream.
Only the tracks that I select.
So that's awesome.
I gotta do that.
But I can't do it right now.
I have to fix it while I'm offline and then...
Does that mean we get singing balls back?
I'm not actually sure.
So on their website, it does say you're not allowed to use this for commercial purposes.
Isn't this technically a commercial purpose because there is money involved?
But then again, playing copyrighted music such as, I don't know, like Eminem.
That should also be an issue, shouldn't it?
But people do that anyway all the time.
I mean, as long as you don't have it in the VOD.
This wouldn't be commercial purpose.
Are you sure?
The only problem is if you start singing or dancing on this music.
Oh really?
Why would singing balls be copyrighted?
It's because the person in charge of the website has spent a lot of time actually making those sounds because it's randomly generated as you go along.
It's not just a track.
Like effort went into it, you know?
I'll record your own singing balls.
Maybe I should.
But I mean, think about it.
A lot of big streamers in World of Warcraft specifically.
Uh, let me see here.
Let me see who's live right now.
Probably...
I don't know.
Also people who stream Starcraft, you know?
Like Rotterdam, Artosis or Grubby, Neuro.
They all play just normal music from Spotify while they play, right?
But it doesn't show up in the VOD.
So I think that's fine.
I should be able to play whatever.
What if you sit with a bowl and start singing?
Now, that's a different thing.
Heh heh.
As long as you don't make money from it, it's not commercial use.
I see what you mean.
News of PE, but...
I don't know.
Like, I'm not allowed to use it in in my project and this could be considered a project of sorts, no?
Who knows?
I mean, I haven't had an issue with it.
It's probably not a big deal.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna be out of here.
It's time to eat some food.